<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!--SHARED-->
		<!--Mythical Beast-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CULDIV_MYTHICAL_BEAST">
			<Text>Mythical Beast</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CULDIV_MYTHICAL_BEAST_DESC">
			<Text>{1_Desc}[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CULDIV_MYTHICAL_BEAST_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CULDIV_MYTHICAL_BEAST_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>What nonsense!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CULDIV_MYTHICAL_BEAST_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have dismissed claims of the existence of the mythical {1_Weirdness}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CULDIV_MYTHICAL_BEAST_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} {2_Yield}[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_CULDIV_MYTHICAL_BEAST">
			<Text>Evidence of the mythical {1_Weirdness} has been found {@2_CivName: plural 2?by; other?in;} {2_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ANDEAN-->
		<!--Huaca-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ANDEAN">
			<Text>Huaca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ANDEAN_DESC">
			<Text>Our priests have commemorated a new Huaca - a new site deemed holy and sacred. We should see to it that our people honour this site with a ceremony.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ANDEAN_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>We shall fund this ceremony ourselves.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ANDEAN_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>We shall force the nobility to fund this ceremony.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ANDEAN_OUTCOME_3">
			<Text>We shall let the priests fund this ceremony.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ANDEAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lose {1_Num} [ICON_GOLD] Gold[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {2_Num} {3_Yield}[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ANDEAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Each city has a 30% chance to go into [ICON_RESISTANCE] Resistance for one turn[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_PEACE] Faith[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ANDEAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_3">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Nothing[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_ANDEAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have funded an elaborate ceremony in order to celebrate a new holy site.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_ANDEAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have forced the nobility to fund an elaborate ceremony in order to celebrate a new holy site.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_ANDEAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2_ALT_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have forced the nobility to fund an elaborate ceremony in order to celebrate a new holy site. They were not, however, pleased with this decision.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_ANDEAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_3_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have allowed the priests to fund an elaborate ceremony in order to celebrate a new holy site.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Andean: Cherufe-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_01">
			<Text>Cherufe</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_01_DESC">
			<Text>Recently, strange balls of black fire have been raining down over a village near {1_CityName}, said to arise from where an evil beast known as the Cherufe - a lizard made of magma and fire - dwells at the pit of a laval pool. We must kill this beast if we are to hope for this phenomenon to end.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We should rally the guard and hunt down this beast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have brought peace to those tormented by the legendary Cherufe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Andean: Kari Kari-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_02">
			<Text>Kari Kari</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_02_DESC">
			<Text>The Kari-Kari is a beastly man of legend, whom adorns the clothes of a priest and haunts the slumbering in search of fat and grease for his otherworldy and magical purposes. But we have evidence to believe that this creature of the night is merely one of our own; a malignant shaman using the cover of conspiracy to commit his thefts and blasphemies.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>This man should be brought to justice.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have brought peace to those tormented by the legendary Kari Kari.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Andean: Anchimayen -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_03">
			<Text>Anchimayen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_03_DESC">
			<Text>Several of our villages have been terrorized by the black magic of kalku sorcerers. Using the corpses of children, these kalku create anchimayen, which resemble small children but can change into flying fireballs! The actions of these kalku blatantly insult the laws of our empire. Should we find these sorcerers and bring them to justice?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Find them! For the children!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>To the rejoice of our people, we have managed to capture those responsible for the use of balck magic within our empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Andean: Ukuku -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_04">
			<Text>Ukuku</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_04_DESC">
			<Text>In some mountainous areas of our empire, it is said that bears have begun to copy human mating behavior. These ukuku allegedly steal teenage girls from their families and hold them hostage in a cave. Then they steal food from our farmers as 'gifts' to their 'wife.' The kidnapped girls eventually have two sons. These sons, while supposedly not malevolent, possess so much strength that they accidentally kill the people they try to play with. They are also said to kill their father, to their mother's understandable delight. What should we do in response to such stories?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>Theft? Rape? Murder? Find and destroy these ukuku!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The destruction of several crminial ukuku is something to rejoice.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Andean: Lik'ichiri -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_05">
			<Text>Lik'ichiri</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_05_DESC">
			<Text>It is said that villagers who live in the mountains of our empire are visited by a spirit that slices open their bodies to take their fat. Its victims often don't know that they've been cut open, but if they do not receive help, they usually die. If that weren't bad enough, a few villagers have begun to emulate this "lik'ichiri," stealing fat from others and absconding with it for unknown purposes.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_05_BUTTON">
			<Text>At least we won't have an obesity problem!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_05_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The lowering of morality rates from obesity related illnesses is cause for celebration.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Andean: Huallepen -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_06">
			<Text>Huallepen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_06_DESC">
			<Text>Distraught mothers in our empire are complaining of encounters with a creature they call a huallepen. It is said to be so ugly that if a pregnant woman were to lay eyes upon it for three consecutive nights that their unborn child would be horribly disfigured. Understandably, some fathers have attempted to find and deal with the creatures in the lakes and rivers they call home, but were driven away by violent attacks. For the sake of their children, the villagers request that we deal with the creatures.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_06_BUTTON">
			<Text>Of course! There shall be no ugly babies in the empire!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_06_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The death of ugly babies has eradicated several awkward faus pax's from our empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Andean: Alicanto-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_07">
			<Text>Alicanto</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_07_DESC">
			<Text>Workers in our mines have claimed to see a most spectacular bird during the night. The bird's feathers are said to shine with metallic colors and its eyes give off strange light as well. A few of the miners say they've managed to follow this strange bird, which they believe led them to deposits of gold or silver. The ones unlucky enough to get caught, they say, are guided off a cliff to their deaths. This bird, if real, could lead us to untold riches.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_07_BUTTON">
			<Text>Track this bird!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_07_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The appearance of the mythical Alicanto has inspired us to track its whereabouts.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Andean: Huallepen -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_08">
			<Text>Saxra</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_08_DESC">
			<Text>Some of our faithful are beginning to cease going to the chullpas, fearing "spirits of the bones." These saxra are supposedly under the thrall of "el Diablo," and a close encounter with one is said to result in a variety of illnesses, or even the loss of one's soul. The priests have begun to complain of dwindling attendance for evening ceremonies, as the spirits are allegedly active at night. What should we do to keep our chullpas active?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_08_BUTTON">
			<Text>At the cost of our soul? Pray at home!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ANDEAN_08_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Advising that our faithful pray in the safety of their homes, we have surely saved their souls from the terrible saxra.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--BANTU-->
		<!--Great Migration-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BANTU">
			<Text>Great Migration</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BANTU_DESC">
			<Text>
				A great period of migration has begun. People from the south have made the long journey across the land to our civilization, hoping that we might welcome them into our cities.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BANTU_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>We shall accept these migrants.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BANTU_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>These migrants have no place in our empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BANTU_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive +1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Population in all cities[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BANTU_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive {1_Num} [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age points[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_BANTU_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have accepted migrants into our empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_BANTU_OUTCOME_RESULT_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have turned away migrants from our empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_BANTU">
			<Text>A great migration has begun toward the {1_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Bantu: Umkovu-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_01">
			<Text>Umkovu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_01_DESC">
			<Text>For days a village on the outskirts of {1_CityName} had been plagued by a curse which summoned from the other world hordes of the umkovu - the living dead, come from their graves in search of flesh which to devour. But a local shaman has finally concocted of a ritual to lift this curse, and the people of this village can finally be free of their living nightmares.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We can breathe a sigh of relief.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A curse which had raised the dead from their graves has been lifted over our people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Bantu: Emela-ntouka-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_02">
			<Text>Emela-ntouka</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_02_DESC">
			<Text>Some of our villagers have begun to share tales of a large, growling beast that lives near various bodies of water in our empire. While they say it is horned, they do not agree on the number. But they do agree that this beast is very aggressive and has even disemboweled elephants with its horns! It supposedly eats plants, but the villagers still live in constant fear of encountering one.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Show them we have nothing to fear from this beast!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have sent a guard to kill the feared Emela-ntouka, and have brought peace of mind to the village that it was terrorising.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Bantu: Grootslang-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_03">
			<Text>Grootslang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_03_DESC">
			<Text>Several villagers are rattled by the recent appearance of what they describe to be an ancient, primordial snake. The creature is noted for its cruelty, able to eat even elephants, but the villagers say it is also extremely greedy and that people can buy their freedom if they have enough precious gems. In particular, they avoid a diamond-filled cave they call "the Bottomless Pit."</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Search the cave and destroy this creature!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>By good fortune, we have managed to hunt down the terrible Grootslang and have slain it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Bantu: Ya-te-veo-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_04">
			<Text>Ya-te-veo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_04_DESC">
			<Text>Hunters have begun to return to towns throughout the empire, telling tales of man-eating trees that terrorize our interior forests. They say the trees move, as if they were a bundle of snakes tied together. If an unwary person wanders too close, the trees snap at them. Those it catches are crushed to death in its branches, which drink the victim's blood through innumerable mouths. Some of the hunters are refusing to find food for our empire out of fear of these trees.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>Cleanse our forests of these terrors!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BANTU_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>To restore peace amongst our hunters, we have ensured that the threat of any Ya-te-veo is destroyed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--BHARATA-->
		<!--Spiritual Leader-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BHARATA">
			<Text>Spiritual Leader</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BHARATA_DESC">
			<Text>
				A new spiritual leader has begun to attract many followers within our empire. Their ideas are not dissimilar to our own, but there are those who feel that their teachings may disrupt the fragile peace that exists between the religious minorities in our empire.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BHARATA_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>We must put a stop to their teachings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BHARATA_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>We must embrace their teachings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BHARATA_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive 2 free Inquisitors and a free Missionary[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_BHARATA_OUTCOME_2_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive a free Great Prophet[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_BHARATA_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have put a stop to the teachings of a new spiritual leader.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_BHARATA_OUTCOME_RESULT_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have embraced the teachings of a new spiritual leader.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_BHARATA_1">
			<Text>{1_LeaderName} has put an end to the teachings of a new spiritual leader in the {2_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_BHARATA_2">
			<Text>{1_LeaderName} has embraced the teachings of a new spiritual leader in the {2_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Bharata: Yeti-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_01">
			<Text>Yeti</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_01_DESC">
			<Text>We have heard tales of an ape-like creature which lives far to the north; amidst the deadliest of snowstorms, at the peak of the highest of mountains. We know not whether this creature be man or ape, but we know it not to be beast, for we have heard the tales of its acts of heroism to save those adventurers who would otherwise surely perish on the treacherous slopes.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We should honour this creature.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have honoured the fabled Yeti, a creature purported to aide weary adventurers who face otherwise certain death on the treacherous mountainsides.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Bharata: Garuda-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_02">
			<Text>Garuda</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_02_DESC">
			<Text>Priests have begun to spread stories of Garuda, whom they say has the body and limbs of a man, but head, talons, wings and beak of an eagle. This creature is said to be very noble protector of our empire, defending the faithful from evil. Their message has begun to catch on in some local villages. Should the empire take an official stance on its existence?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Give it room in our temples!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Our honouring of the Garuda will surely pay off.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Bharata: Rakshasa-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_03">
			<Text>Rakshasa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_03_DESC">
			<Text>Rumors of a vicious being that prowls the countryside of our empire have begun to turn into cries for help. This creature is said to be enormous, with fangs, sharp claws, flaming red eyes and hair, and a taste for human blood. They are also allegedly able to fly, change size at will, and turn invisible, allowing them to elude the local search parties. Fear of these "demons" has begun to spread throughout our empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us find and defeat this creature!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_BHARATA_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We can rest easy knowing that the Rakshasa has ben defeated.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--CENTRAL-->
		<!--Dynastic Union-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CENTRAL">
			<Text>Dynastic Union</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CENTRAL_DESC">
			<Text>
				A blushing bride from {1_CityStateName} has recently been wed to one of our cousins, and with this marriage has come a closer union between our two nations. Let us hope for many years of harmony between us![NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CENTRAL_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>A glorious celebration for the nobility!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CENTRAL_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>A day for all to celebrate!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CENTRAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence with {2_CityStateName}[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CENTRAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All cities begin celebrating 'We Love the King Day' for 2 turns[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence with {2_CityStateName}[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_CENTRAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A bride from a powerful family in {1_CityStateName} has been wed to our cousin, creating a dynastic union between our two families.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_CENTRAL">
			<Text>A dynastic union has been celebrated between the ruling families of {1_CivName} and the city-state of {2_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Central: White Lady-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_01">
			<Text>White Lady</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_01_DESC">
			<Text>While investigating the attic of an old, derelict castle in the outskirts of {1_City}, a local nobleman was confronted by a ghost of a woman. The phantom was combing its hair and basking in the bright light of the midday sun, entering the attic through the run-down roof. Turned out this White Lady was the ghost of one of the noble's ancestresses, and appeared to be benevolent. After completing the Lady's request - explanation of which the nobleman prudently avoided - he was granted access to the family treasury, entrance to which was littered with bones of less resourceful burglars. There was enough money for him to renovate the castle and reinvigorate the entire nearby fief. The nobleman holds a big feast to celebrate this event.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We can't miss the party!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have accepted an invitation to feast at a haunted castle.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Central: Rokita-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_02">
			<Text>Rokita</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_02_DESC">
			<Text>The innkeeper from a crossroads tavern near {1_City} managed to fool and capture - with the help of his fellow priest and constable - the petty devil Rokita. A great trickster, he would prank our subjects in a variety of ways and use clever magic to enchant and rob them blind. The vile little man appears to be very drunk and continues to fling obscene words at our ears. We hope to put him to justice and lock him forever in the deepest of dungeons. Over are the days of Rokita leading packs of highwaymen and robbing hapless peasants and travellers within our empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us hope he doesn't escape!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have captured the petty devil Rokita.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Central: Wolpertinger-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_03">
			<Text>Wolpertinger</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_03_DESC">
			<Text>As they were packing up and getting ready to go home, a band of woodcutters from a village near {1_City} spotted an eerie animal watching them from the forest. It looked like a large rabbit, but with big antlers and hawk wings. The men managed to ambush and capture the creature and brought it back to their village. This is the first time our people can see a Wolpertinger!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Those folk tales were true!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have learned of the terrible Wolpertinger and died a little inside.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Central: Werewolf-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_04">
			<Text>Werewolf</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_04_DESC">
			<Text>Tales of werewolves haunting local villages are common throughout our empire, but no evidence had yet been found to support these stories. But a local village near the city of {1_CityName} has finally resolved to hunt down the beasts which had been picking off their livestock and devouring their children. They have managed to capture and kill one, and have its pelt as proof. We could use this opportunity to organise a guard to hunt these monsters to extinction.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>An age in which we are not plagued by these attacks is dawning.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have resolved to organise a mission to hunt down and exterminate the werewolf plague.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Central: Basilisk-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_05">
			<Text>Basilisk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_05_DESC">
			<Text>A local hero from the city of {1_CityName} claims that they have captured and slain the mighty Basilisk - the King of Serpents. The Basilisk is a monstrous creature - said to kill with its very gaze - but it is vulnerable to the crow of a Rooster. If indeed this beast has been slain, it is a day to celebrate.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_05_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us celebrate the death of the Basilisk.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_05_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We begin celebrations in honour of the slaying of the monstrous Basilisk.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Central: Poltergeist-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_06">
			<Text>Poltergeist</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_06_DESC">
			<Text>A member of the local clergy has come to our court, requesting divine help from our empire's highest religious officials. He claims that a family in his city is tormented by a malevolent spirit; a poltergeist, he calls it. This spirit terrorizes the family by throwing items around the house at random and knocking loudly on the walls, and his claims are backed by the written testimony of several citizens who claim to have seen objects fly about the house without explanation. Should we give the priest the assistance he requests?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_06_BUTTON">
			<Text>Send an old priest and a young priest!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_06_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The poltergeist menace appears to have been sedated by our divine aide.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Central: Frankenstein's monster-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_07">
			<Text>Frankenstein's monster</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_07_DESC">
			<Text>Citizens of {1_CityName} claim that a mad scientist, Victor Frankenstein, locked away on his laboratory atop a mountain near the city, has harnessed the power of a recent thunderstorm to bring an abomination to life. Frankenstein's monster, as it has been called, was created by stitching together pieces of the city's dead. Its grotesque appearance terrifies all who run across the beast. One citizen even claims that the monster attempted to kidnap his daughter!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_07_BUTTON">
			<Text>Kill it with fire!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CENTRAL_07_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have killed Frankenstein's monster.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--CLASSICAL-->
		<!--Philosophical Debate-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL">
			<Text>Philosophical Debate</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC">
			<Text>
				Two eminent philosophers have launched a heated and public attack against one another, in dispute of each other's ideas. The topic at hand is {1_Philosophy}. Whilst interesting, their display is beginning to upset the less sophisticated of our citizens, and we must decide who is right.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_1">
			<Text>on the morality of war</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_2">
			<Text>on the duties of government</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_3">
			<Text>on the divisibility of sovereignty</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_4">
			<Text>on the cuddliness of kittens</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_5">
			<Text>on the existence of existence</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_6">
			<Text>on just economics</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_7">
			<Text>on the interpretation of colours</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_8">
			<Text>on the nature of man</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_9">
			<Text>on choice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_10">
			<Text>on the prevarication of moddability</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_11">
			<Text>on the wealth of beggars</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_12">
			<Text>on the interpretation of coughing</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_13">
			<Text>on the spirit of law</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_14">
			<Text>on the state of nature</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_15">
			<Text>on the sexiest world leader</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_16">
			<Text>on the rights of the indigenous</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_17">
			<Text>on the banality of evil</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_18">
			<Text>on the nutrition of dust</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_19">
			<Text>on depressive realism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_DESC_20">
			<Text>"on the use of non-violence</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>Clearly we must favour the realist argument.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>We must concede to the subjectivist position.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All units gain 5 XP[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age points[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_CLASSICAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have settled a heated, philosophical dispute {1_Debate}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_CLASSICAL">
			<Text>A philosophical debate {1_Debate} is ongoing in the {2_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Classical: Hydra-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_01">
			<Text>Hydra</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_01_DESC">
			<Text>The Hydra is an ancient serpent with many heads; said to be poisonous of blood and breath and said to, for every head severed, grow two more. Only the great hero, Heracles, has been known in legend to have slain one successfully. Tales of Heracles' cunning are re-told in our poety and plays, and it is a story to which we should all heed a lesson that removing the head might resolve the body to grow stronger.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We celebrate Heracles' triumph over the Hydra even today.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We celebrate Heracles' triumph over the monstrous and legendary Hydra.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Classical: Sphinx-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_02">
			<Text>Sphinx</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_02_DESC">
			<Text>A strange creature blocks the exit and entrance to the city of {1_CityName}. This creature has the body of a lionness, the head of a woman, the wings of an eagle, and a serpent-headed tail. This is the dreaded Sphinx, which asks of those who cross its path a riddle: "Which creature has one voice and yet becomes four-footed and two-footed and three-footed?" If those who respond give the answer wrong, then the Sphinx shall devour them whole But our scholars have found the answer: it is a man: that which crawls on all fours as a baby, walks on two feet as an adult, and uses a walking stick in old age. Our advisors recommend that we send someone to the Sphinx with this answer, and so the city can be free again.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>We must stop this strange siege. Send him now!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have successfully answered the Sphinx's riddle, and it has left us in peace.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Classical: Sirens-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_03">
			<Text>Sirens</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_03_DESC">
			<Text>Fishermen and traders that frequent the coastal cities of our empire have begun to avoid a rocky area outside {1_CityName}. They claim that women of extreme beauty live there, luring unlucky sailors to their deaths with an irresistible song. Searches to find the missing ships have not found the women, but there are many shipwrecks in the area, more than anywhere else in the empire. A few of the searchers claimed to have heard their hypnotic song, but their crewmates tied them to the mast of their ships and plugged their ears with wax. Should we continue to search for these women?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Yes, and be sure to take ear plugs!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A Golden Age begins because reasons.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Classical: Phoenix-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_04">
			<Text>Phoenix</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_04_DESC">
			<Text>Citizens of {1_CityName} speak of a beautiful bird that had made its home in their city. The bird is said to have been a most pleasant red and gold, its feathers shining bright as the sun. Some say they were drawn to the city square to see the bird roasting alive in a fire none say they had started. When the fire died down, a young chick rose from the ashes of its parent. They made this phoenix the symbol of their city!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>I wish to see this bird; find it and bring it to me!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A beautiful Phoenix has become a gift to our court.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Classical: Manticore-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_05">
			<Text>Manticore</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_05_DESC">
			<Text>Travelling scholars bring stories about a mysterious creature. Part man, part lion and part scorpion, this creature seems like one of the more prestigious creations of the gods. The tales they tell about its fierceness and the natural weapons it bears strike fear in the populace. </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_05_BUTTON">
			<Text>Find it and destroy it. My people should not live in fear!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_CLASSICAL_05_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Our empire has no more to fear from the horrible Manticore.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--COLONIAL-->
		<!--Independence Day-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_COLONIAL">
			<Text>Independence Day</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_COLONIAL_DESC">
			<Text>
				Independence Day celebrations have begun. On this day, we celebrate our long history of self-determination and the sovereignty of our nation.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_COLONIAL_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>A worthy celebration.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_COLONIAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age points[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]All cities begin celebrating 'We Love the King Day' for one turn[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_COLONIAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Independence Day celebrations have begun.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_COLONIAL">
			<Text>The {1_CivName} celebrates its independence day.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Chubacabra-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_01">
			<Text>Chubacabra</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_01_DESC">
			<Text>One still night a farmer was compelled by a strange noise to check upon his stock. As he stepped from his home, a strange, dog-like beast skittered across his path. For a moment, the beast looked at him, and its eyes glistened red as if with the soul of a demon; a snarl covered in blood. Before the farmer could gather himself, the beast hurried off into the night; but he knew what he had seen: the blood-sucking Chubacabra.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>This is surely evidence of the creature!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have accepted the story of a possibly inebriated farmer as evidence of the fabled Chubacabra.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Alien-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_02">
			<Text>Alien</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_02_DESC">
			<Text>Near to a top secret military base outside the city of {1_CityName}, a strange machine has been discovered. We have been told that the machine contains the corpse of a creature unlike any ever seen before, and it is one disturbing to the senses. Could this be a sign of extraterrestrial life?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>All efforts to study this creature - in secret - should be made.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have recovered what may be evidence of extraterrestrial life.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: TPangolin-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_03">
			<Text>TPangolin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_03_DESC">
			<Text>A frightening discovery has been made in a cave near {1_CityName}, prooving the existence of the elusive and terrifying TPangolin. A huntsman, whilst returning home from a fresh kill, stumbled upon a hidden shrine, adorned with evidence of the beast. The huntsman sensibly fled for his life, but now we must endeavour to capture this horror.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>We must set up a taskforce to capture this creature.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have successfully captured and defenestrated the previously mythical TPangolin.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Bigfoot-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_04">
			<Text>Bigfoot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_04_DESC">
			<Text>Evidence prooving the existence of the elusive Bigfoot - an ape-like creature that was said to be as tall and bad-tempered as a man - has finally been found by a huntsman in a park near {1_CityName}. This is a sign that we must track down this beast for further study.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>We shall assemble a team of scientists and rangers to capture this beast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have successfully captured the once mythical Bigfoot.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Alien Abduction-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_05">
			<Text>Alien Abduction</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_05_DESC">
			<Text>Reports have surfaced that some of our villagers have been abducted by gray creatures with large black eyes on remote roads and even out of their bedrooms. These villagers claim that the beings experiment on them, often with probes. While these reports are still uncommon, if true, these beings would represent a grave threat to the security of our empire. Should we continue to track the reports to determine if the truth is really out there?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_05_BUTTON">
			<Text>Of course! I've got a blue book around here somewhere...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_05_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have found solid evidence of an alien abduction occuring within our empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Mothman-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_06">
			<Text>Mothman</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_06_DESC">
			<Text>Citizens from {1_CityName} have reported seeing an unusual creature. They say it looks like a large, flying man with ten-foot wings and glowing red eyes that follows travellers down a road near an abandoned military factory. One man even claims that the creature, which he calls "Mothman," predicts the collapse of a bridge. Should these claims be investigated?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_06_BUTTON">
			<Text>Search the area for this Mothman!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_06_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We shall begin our search for the Mothman.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Globster-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_07">
			<Text>Globster</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_07_DESC">
			<Text>An unidentified corpse has washed up on our shores. It resembles a mass of boneless flesh, and the locals have begun to call the creature a "globster." The sudden appearance of a creature this size is unsettling and may represent the vanguard of an unknown terror from the deep.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_07_BUTTON">
			<Text>Poke it with a stick!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_07_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have pocked a disturbing, gelatinous blob with a stick, triggering a Golden Age!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Skaz881-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_08">
			<Text>Skaz881</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_08_DESC">
			<Text>Tales of a most helpful creature have surfaced in {1_CityName}. Patient and determined, the Skaz881 is said to sassily aide people in hunting down and exterminating nasty and obscure bugs.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_08_BUTTON">
			<Text>Wonderful news!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_08_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have heard tale of the Skaz881.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Manbearpig-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_09">
			<Text>Manbearpig</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_09_DESC">
			<Text>We have recently been approached by a world renown scholar on mythical beasts. They claim that a creature that is half-man, half-bear, and half-pig has been spotted stalking the streets of {1_CityName}, and they offer their services to hunt down the beast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_09_BUTTON">
			<Text>It is agreed. Any beast that threatens our people must be dealt with.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_09_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have managed to hunt and capture the elusive Manbearpig.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Slender Man -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_10">
			<Text>Slender Man</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_10_DESC">
			<Text>Several reports of the mysterious disappearance of children from {1_CityName} have been brought to our attention. Photographs of the children from periods just prior to their disappearance show a tall, slender figure with long, tentacle-like arms and a featureless face dressed in a suit. Some of the city's locals are terrified of the creature, which they claim can teleport, and most who claim to have had close contact with the creature have become paranoid and subject to nosebleeds. Though many citizens claim that the disappearances must be rational in nature, a vocal minority are demanding that we deal with the creature.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_10_BUTTON">
			<Text>Hide the children!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_10_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The hiding of our nation's children from Slender Man has spared many lives.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Bermuda Triangle-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_11">
			<Text>Bermuda Triangle</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_11_DESC">
			<Text>The captains of our trade vessels have begun to refuse contracts for shipping routes that pass through a patch of ocean they claim to be supernatural. Several claim that ships and planes have gone into the area, never to return or be heard from again. Some say that they've successfully completed the voyage, but were enveloped by an otherwordly fog and that their compasses began to act up. They feel they were lucky enough to cross the first time; they are not willing to do so again. Should we redraw our trade routes to avoid this area?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_11_BUTTON">
			<Text>Of course! What if I were on a ship that disappeared there?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_11_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Ship disappearances have dramatically decreased since we re-drew our trade routes to avoid the Bermuda Triangle.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Jersey Devil-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_12">
			<Text>Jersey Devil</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_12_DESC">
			<Text>In a certain wooded area of your domain, strange screams are heard. The locals attribute this to the Jersey Devil, a creature which possesses the head of a goat, bat-like wings, horns, tiny arms, clawed hands, cloven hooves, and a forked tail. They say it was originally the baby of a Mother Leeds who claimed her thirteen child would be the devil! Some farmers have claimed to see the beast flying near their fields!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_12_BUTTON">
			<Text>This abomination must be destroyed!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_12_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The Jersey Devil shall haunt us no more!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Colonial: Predator-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_13">
			<Text>Predator</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_13_DESC">
			<Text>In the more remote parts of the empire, legends say that on the hottest of summers, men and women have vanished from villages and towns, their bodies found later to have been butchered like animals -- sometimes having been skinned alive, sometimes even worse. As another hot summer passes by, more bodies have been found in this state -- some of them even skilled fighters and soldiers. Whatever is hunting down these people must be stopped!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_13_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us send out an elite special forces team to hunt down this predator!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_COLONIAL_13_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Although we have failed to defeat the evil that is the Predators, we were able to make a film about it along the way.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--EASTERN-->
		<!--Great Assembly-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_EASTERN">
			<Text>Great Assembly</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_EASTERN_DESC">
			<Text>
				A great assembly has been called between all sound and wise men of the nation to offer us counsel. They propose that matters of state and law be discussed in a democratic fashion, but that the word of their ruler remain governing and final.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_EASTERN_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>I will not allow this.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_EASTERN_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>I will allow it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_EASTERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive {1_Num} [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age points[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_EASTERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive {1_Num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_EASTERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have disallowed a great assembly to be gathered to discuss state matters.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_EASTERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have allowed a great assembly to be gathered to discuss state matters.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_EASTERN">
			<Text>A great assembly has been called between members of the upper strata in the {1_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Eastern: Rarog-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_01">
			<Text>Rarog</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_01_DESC">
			<Text>A band of our household warriors were patrolling the countryside outside {1_City} when they were met with an unusual sight. A fiery bird in the shape of a falcon with the tail of a peafowl appeared before the men in a small forest clearing, filling it almost completely with blinding light. It is said that this bird - the Rarog - is a manifestation of the chief sun god, Svarog, and is a symbol of purity, boldness and cleansing fire. This sight left such an impression on our soldiers that some of them even emblazoned their shields with an image of the fire-bird.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>The Gods still watch after us, it's a good omen!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have witnessed a visage of the legendary Rarog.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Eastern: Strzyga-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_02">
			<Text>Strzyga</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_02_DESC">
			<Text>At a great loss of life, the brave guards in one of the towns deep in the forests have killed and decapitated the evil demon Striga, a repulsive, undead woman. Born with two souls, a Striga is raised back to life after the death of its first soul. It extends its existence by feeding on people's life force. It was caught in flagranti, while draining blood out of one of our unlucky subjects wandering the woods at night. With the monster's death, the torment of this settlement is over, as is the owl population of the surrounding forest - exterminated out of fear, as the Striga can take the form of an owl.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Now we know we can fight back!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have slain the wicked Strzyga.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Eastern: Baba Yaga-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_03">
			<Text>Baba Yaga</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_03_DESC">
			<Text>Baba Yaga, the terrifying old hag, has been finally put to rest by one of our witch hunters. Her vile magic, toxic potions and wretched looks long have been bringing despair to many of the villages throughout our empire. With her gone, the peasants can finally return to their ordinary lives, without fear of death or, in the best case, visual trauma.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>She only belongs in the folklore.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The wicked Baba Yaga has been slain.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Eastern: Likho-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_04">
			<Text>Likho</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_04_DESC">
			<Text>Villagers in the rural areas of our empire have begun to speak of a creature called a likho. Sometimes the creature punishes the greedy by forcing them to cut their hand off to be rid of a stolen item. Other times it hops onto a person's back and rides them; it is said that a few have tried to drown the creature, only to drown themselves and allow the creature to terrorize others. All the stories agree that the creature looks like an old woman in a black dress, but with only one large eye on her face. Should we follow up on these claims?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>Yes, get to the bottom of this likho!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Resolving to investigate reports of the Likho has aided in the arrest of a common criminal who appears to have been behind the legend.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Eastern: Black Volga-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_05">
			<Text>Black Volga</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_05_DESC">
			<Text>Rumors have begun to spread of a sinister black car appearing throughout our empire. Some stories claim the driver kidnaps his victims to harvest their organs or use their blood in demonic rituals. Others claim that the driver asks passerby for the time, killing them when they approach or even claim the victims die at the exact same time the next day! Because this black car is the same color and model as those reserved for government work, citizens have become nervous at the sight of government officials conducting legitimate business.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_05_BUTTON">
			<Text>Find this car and bring the driver to justice!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_EASTERN_05_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>As it turns out, the owner of the Black Volga was none other than one of our government officials. They have been fired, and their licence to drive confiscated.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ISLAMIC-->
		<!--Trade Rights-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ISLAMIC">
			<Text>Trading Rights</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ISLAMIC_DESC">
			<Text>
				Our lucrative goods and shrewd merchants have managed to secure for us a exclusive trade deal with a foreign merchant. We should make the most of this opportunity.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ISLAMIC_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>These trading rights could be sold for the right price.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ISLAMIC_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>Send our greatest merchants to take advantage of these trading rights.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ISLAMIC_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive {1_Num} [ICON_GOLD] Gold[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ISLAMIC_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive a free Great Merchant[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_ISLAMIC_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have sold our exclusive trading rights to a foreign merchant.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_ISLAMIC_OUTCOME_RESULT_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have sent our greatest merchants to take advantage of our recent trade agreement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_ISLAMIC">
			<Text>Merchants {@1_CivName: plural 2?amongst; other?in;} {1_CivName} have secured a trade deal with a wealthy entrepeneur.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Islamic: Djinn-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_01">
			<Text>Djinn</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_01_DESC">
			<Text>The Djinn, or Genies, are said to be one of the three sapient creations of God; like humans, they, too, are said to be of free will. They dwell in an unseen world, beyond this universe, and were said to have stood behind the court of Solomon. There are those which are wicked; which torment our universe. But then there are those which are good; which bring kindness and compassion to those in need.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We should honour those Djinn which are benevolant toward us.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have honoured the benevolant Djinn who would seek good will of our people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Islamic: Ghoul-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_02">
			<Text>Ghoul</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_02_DESC">
			<Text>Shapeshifting demons have been spotted living in the arid, sandy regions of our empire. It is said that these ghouls can take the form of hyenas, leading hunters into the desert wastes, never to be seen again. Those who have seen them and lived to tell the tale claim that they feast on our dead and can take the form of the person whose body they last ate from. People have begun to flock to places of worship to pray for protection from this gruesome beast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Slay this eater of our dead!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The slaying of a Ghoul has given peace to our people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Islamic: Rukh-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_03">
			<Text>Rukh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_03_DESC">
			<Text>Herders in our empire have begun to complain of their herds thinning. They say that a gigantic eagle, a rukh, much larger than a man, grabs one of their animals and drops it from a great height. The poor animals are killed on impact and eaten in the rukh's own time. Supposedly, one man attempted to end the threat to his herds by tracking the beast back to its nest to kill it and its young. Apparently, he has not been seen since. What should we do?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Succeed where that man failed!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The capture of the terrible Rukh shall ensure that our empire's herd-animals are safe once more.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Islamic: Buraq-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_04">
			<Text>Rukh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_04_DESC">
			<Text>There have been reports of a marvelous winged steed flying in the clouds above {1_CityName} and the marketplaces are getting crowded by people hoping to catch a glimpse of it. If we could somehow convince it to stay around, it could attract quite a few merchants and tourists to {1_CityName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>Bring it in, I will make it the royal mount!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ISLAMIC_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A wonderful Rukh has, since capture, attracted many people to our empire in order to gaze upon it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--KATUJE-->
		<!--Great Hunt-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_KATUJE">
			<Text>Great Hunt</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_KATUJE_DESC">
			<Text>A local tribe has decided to organize a great hunt in order to track down a beast that has been snatching their young as of late. They have petitioned us to provide them with the tools to do this.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_KATUJE_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>We shall certainly play our part.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_KATUJE_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lose {1_Num} [ICON_GOLD] Gold[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain 2 Ranged Units at the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital.[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_KATUJE_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have agreed to fund a great hunt against an animal killing our young.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_KATUJE_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>They'll have to find funding somewhere else.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_KATUJE_OUTCOME_2_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Nothing[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_KATUJE_OUTCOME_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have declined to fund a great hunt against an animal killing our young</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Katuje: Ipupiara -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_01">
			<Text>Ipupiara</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_01_DESC">
			<Text>The people of {1_City} have begun to report sightings of an Ipupiara in a local river. The creature is said to be the source of a decline in the river's source of fish, and is a menace to the local economy. They have asked that we deal with the beast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We shall organize a hunt to kill it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have hunted and killed a river-creature called the Ipupiara which had been devouring a local source of fish.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Katuje: Mula sem Cabea -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_02">
			<Text>Mula sem Cabeca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_02_DESC">
			<Text>Folks near the road to {1_City} have reported the strange appearance of a headless mule at night. The beast, said to spit fire as it gallops by, has begun to worry several locals, who believe it to be a demon spirit. It has reportedly stopped trade in and out of the city on nights on which it is said to be frequent.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>So we build a new road around it!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have constructed a new road, diverting trade from a path where it is said a headless mule roams.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Katuje: Mula sem Cabea -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_03">
			<Text>Curupira</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_03_DESC">
			<Text>A huntsman returning from a hunt near {1_City} reports sighting a fiery-haired boy with backwards-facing feet. This, they say, is the Curupira - a guardian of the forest that seeks to trap those who hunt for sport amongst the forest's maze.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>So long as we treat nature with respect, we have nothing to fear.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_KATUJE_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have issued warnings throughout our civilization that we must treat the forest with care.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--MANDALA-->
		<!-- White Elephant Found -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MANDALA">
			<Text>White Elephant Found</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MANDALA_DESC">
			<Text>We've managed to get hold of a White Elephant. This is, of course, a very auspicious omen; our nation is guaranteed prosperity in the years to come!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MANDALA_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>This is wonderful news!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MANDALA_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain a source of [ICON_RES_JFD_WHITE_ELEPHANT] White Elephant[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_JFD_WHITE_ELEPHANT">
			<Text>White Elephant</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_JFD_WHITE_ELEPHANT_TEXT">
			<Text>A white elephant (also albino elephant) is a rare kind of elephant, but not a distinct species. Although often depicted as snow white, their skin is normally a soft reddish-brown, turning a light pink when wet. They have fair eyelashes and toenails. The traditional "white elephant" is commonly misunderstood as being albino, but the Thai term chang samkhan, actually translates as 'auspicious elephant', being "white" in terms of an aspect of purity.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_MANDALA">
			<Text>A White Elephant has been discovered in the {1_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Mandala: Phaya Naga-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_01">
			<Text>Phaya Naga</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_01_DESC">
			<Text>Locals in {1_City} report seeing signs of the mythical Phaya Naga; the tracks of a massive serpent have been left and people claim that fireballs were sighted in the sky. The appearance of such a magnificent creature has caused the people to begin preparations for a celebration to honor it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>Aid in the festivities</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have joined in festivities celebrating the sighting of a Phaya Naga.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Mandala: Orang-bati-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_02">
			<Text>Orang-bati</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_02_DESC">
			<Text>Villagers in the jungles of our empire have become uneasy following the disapperance of several children. The villagers say that a creature called an orang-bati stole the children from their beds and flew away to eat them. Some say the creature looks like an orangutan with wings, while others claim it looks like a gigantic flying reptile. No matter what it looks like, they agree that we should deal with the danger to their children.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Ground this beast and find our children!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The terrible Orang-bati has been destroyed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Mandala: Pontianak-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_03">
			<Text>Pontianak</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_03_DESC">
			<Text>Citizens are terrified of a ghostly creature they claim to be the spirit of women who have died while pregnant. They say that the creature locates its victims by the scent on clothes hanging on the line; as a result, many of our subjects refuse to leave clothes out to dry overnight. If it is near, then one can hear the soft cries of a baby, but wails if it is far away. The creature is believed to be malevolent, ripping out organs with its bare hands to eat them, or sucking the eyes from the sockets of those unfortunate enough not to close them when they meet the apparition. During the day, it lives in our banana trees, and supposedly the only way to fend it off is to drive a nail into a hole in its neck.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Distribute nails throughout the empire!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MANDALA_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Attacks from the horrible Pontianak have decreased since arming our citizens with nails.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--MESOAMERICAN-->
		<!--War Captives-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN">
			<Text>War Captives</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_DESC">
			<Text>
				In our ongoing war we have exacted many {1_Adjective} captives from our defeated foes. So many, in fact, that we can no longer keep them as mere prisoners. We must therefore decide their fate: do they gain the honour of becoming a sacrifice? Or do we put them to work back in our capital?[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>We shall sacrifice these capitves in the name of our Gods.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>We shall have these captives sent to work in our capital.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_OUTCOME_3">
			<Text>We shall execute all of these captives, to inspire loyalty in our soldiers.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive {1_Num} {2_Yield}[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive {1_Num} [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_3">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All Land Military Units gain 5 XP[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have sent our war captives to be human sacrifices.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have sent our war captives to hard labour in our capital.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_3_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have executed all of our war captives.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_1">
			<Text>Hundreds of {1_Adjective} war captives have been sacrificed to the {2_Adjective} Gods.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_2">
			<Text>Hundreds of {1_Adjective} war captives have been sent to hard labour in the {2_Adjective} capital.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_MESOAMERICAN_3">
			<Text>Hundreds of {1_Adjective} war captives have been executed by the {2_Adjective} army.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Mesoamerican: Feathered Serpent-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_01">
			<Text>Feathered Serpent</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_01_DESC">
			<Text>Behold! The Feathered Serpent - harbinger of the cosmos - has come forth from the other worlds to the dreams of a priest. It speaks of an offering to which we must oblige, lest our people be cursed by their wicked irreverence.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>A ceremony must be held in honour of the Feathered Serpent.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have honoured the great Feathered Serpent, and good tidings it has brought upon us.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Mesoamerican: Vampire Vines-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_02">
			<Text>Vampire Vines</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_02_DESC">
			<Text>The sites that mark the origins of our empire are said to be infested by vines that feast on animal blood. The vines are covered with a multitude of tiny mouths, through which is devours its meal, leaving the exsanguinated carcass to rot. The mouths also allow the vine to hold tight to its victims; those who manage to escape its grip do so with chunks of flesh torn away. People are afraid to visit these sites to honor our glorious roots.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Rip these weeds from the earth!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The vampire vine menace has been ended.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Mesoamerican: Predator-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_03">
			<Text>Predator</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_03_DESC">
			<Text>In the more remote parts of the empire, legends say that on the hottest of summers, men and women have vanished from villages and towns, their bodies found later to have been butchered like animals -- sometimes having been skinned alive, sometimes even worse. As another hot summer passes by, more bodies have been found in this state -- some of them even skilled fighters and soldiers. Whatever is hunting down these people must be worshipped!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us send out an elite clerical team to pledge worship to these predators!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOAMERICAN_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have begun worshipping the powerful Predators!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--MESOPOTAMIC-->
		<!--Ceremonial Burial-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOPOTAMIC">
			<Text>Ceremonial Burial</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOPOTAMIC_DESC">
			<Text>
				A great member of our family has passed from this world into the next and it has befallen us to oversee their burial. But this of our kin has for long been our rival; perhaps this is our opportunity to exact justice.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOPOTAMIC_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>Damn their heart to be eaten for eternity.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOPOTAMIC_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>Now that they have passed, they must be forgiven, and given a proper burial.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOPOTAMIC_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOPOTAMIC_OUTCOME_2_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_PEACE] Faith[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOPOTAMIC_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have denied one of our kin a proper burial.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_MESOPOTAMIC_OUTCOME_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have agreed to give one of our kin a proper burial.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_MESOPOTAMIC">
			<Text>An important {1_CivAdj} official has passed away.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Mesopotamic: Salawa-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_01">
			<Text>Salawa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_01_DESC">
			<Text>A priest of the city of {1_CityName} has been struck down with blindness. At the dead of night, a jackal-like beast with forked tail and downwards nose crossed the path of a temple devoted to one of our Gods. The beast turned its gaze to our misfortunate priest, and drew him into a piercing and soulless stare. This was a manifestation of the wicked God Set, and we are grateful that he saw fit to only blind the Priest, and not kill him. We have clearly done wrong by Set that he would enter into one of our sacred temples.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>An offering to Set must be made immediately.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have made an offering in the hopes to appease the God Set.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Mesopotamic: Griffin-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_02">
			<Text>Griffin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_02_DESC">
			<Text>A nomad has claimed to have followed a griffin to its home, where he says the beast greedily guards its priceless treasures and possessions. Winged, with the head and front talons of an eagle, and the powerful hindquarters of a lion, the beast is supposedly very powerful. Before coming to us, the nomad has attempted to gain the support of fellow nomads, who all turned him down, claiming that the creature is just, noble and should be left alone. They caution us to let the creature be while the nomad claims it guards riches beyond our wildest dreams and awaits our decision to support him in his quest.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us claim these riches!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have claimed riches having been guarded by a griffen, and glory has been bestown upon our empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Mesopotamic: Gozer-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_03">
			<Text>Gozer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_03_DESC">
			<Text>The Traveller has come! Perched atop the tallest building in our empire, Gozer the Gozerian has opened a portal to its godly dimension. Gozer claims that the end of the world is upon us, and that our destruction is imminent. Those who have tried to reason with Gozer have been killed by the godly being, which demands that we select the form it will take when it destroys us.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Choose the form of the Destructor!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_MESOPOTAMIC_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>I'm not sure I get the reference.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--NORTHERN-->
		<!--Midsummer's Day-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_NORTHERN">
			<Text>Midsummer's Day</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_NORTHERN_DESC">
			<Text>
				The summer solstice has begun and so with it has begun the Midsummer's Day celebrations. Bonfires shall be lit throughout the nation, and there will be plenty of food and drink for all.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_NORTHERN_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>Let is join in the festivities!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_NORTHERN_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>Let us contribute a bit to the festivities!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_NORTHERN_OUTCOME_3">
			<Text>Let us contribute a lot to the festivities!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_NORTHERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All cities begin celebrating 'We Love the King Day' for 3 turns[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_NORTHERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lose {1_Num} [ICON_GOLD][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All cities begin celebrating 'We Love the King Day' for 6 turns[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_NORTHERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_3">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lose {1_Num} [ICON_GOLD][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All cities begin celebrating 'We Love the King Day' for 12 turns[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_NORTHERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The Midsummer's Day celebrations have begun throughout the empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_NORTHERN">
			<Text>Midsummer's Day celebrations have begun in the {1_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Northern: Loch Ness Monster-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_01">
			<Text>Loch Ness Monster</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_01_DESC">
			<Text>One of our revered natural scientists has stumbled across a beast in the murky waters of one of our distant lakes near {1_CityName}. He has evidence, so we are fairly sure this is a legitimate concern.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>Those folk tales were true!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have come across evidence of the existence of the Loch Ness Monster.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Northern: Valkyrie-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_02">
			<Text>Valkyrie</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_02_DESC">
			<Text>Charging across the heavens with fury and rage set in their minds, the Valkyries are creatures to be feared. However, we have heard news that one has been captured and killed by a mob - a joyous day for the terrified citizens of {1_City}! How should we celebrate?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>With verocity, of course!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We celebrate the capture and death of a legendary Valkyrie.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Northern: Kraken-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_03">
			<Text>Kraken</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_03_DESC">
			<Text>A proud sailor tells of his triumph over the mighty Kraken; a monstrous sea beast which devours ships and sinks men to their graves. He offers to teach us the way of killing these beasts, so that our navy might sail the open ocean without fear.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHEN_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>We must indulge the sailors's wisdom.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have indulged in the wisdom of a sailor who claims to have killed a Kraken.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Northern: Neck-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_04">
			<Text>Neck</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_04_DESC">
			<Text>Ridiculous claims have been made by our subjects that there live undiscovered creatures in our lakes and ponds. They say they take the forms of horses or ugly men and lure people into their domains to drown and devour them. These creatures are called 'Necks'. What shall we do?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHEN_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>We can only investigate these claims.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have invesitgated claims of violent and hideous creatures living in our lakes. Unfortunately, these creatures proved to either be elusive, or imaginary. Probably imaginary.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Northern: Nisse-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_05">
			<Text>Nisse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_05_DESC">
			<Text>Our farmers claim to have spotted small, bearded men with red caps and wool sweaters. They allegedliy live in the farmers' sheds and barns, helping the animals, as long as they get a tribute of nice food and drink every so often. They call the creature a 'Nisse'. Should we investigate these claims?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHEN_05_BUTTON">
			<Text>Absolutely investigate these reports.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_05_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have investigated reports of the appearance of creatures called Nisse. Unfortunately, they turned out to merely be southerners. It was an entertaining investigation, however.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Northern: Hulder-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_06">
			<Text>Hulder</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_06_DESC">
			<Text>A creature has been spotted in the outskirts of {1_CityName}. The citizens say it is a 'Hulder', a female with a tail that'll seduce our men and take them to the mountains for the rest of eternity. We cannot let this madness continue!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHEN_06_BUTTON">
			<Text>We must hunt down this wicked succubus.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_06_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have managed to hunt down and slay what was claimed as a Hulder.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Northern: Zantonius Hamm-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_07">
			<Text>Zantonius Hamm</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_07_DESC">
			<Text>A most odd and poetic creature has been reported as being a local attraction in the city of {1_CityName}. The creature is known as the Zantonius Hamm, and is believed to be a shape-shifting walrus. The creature reportedly is an informant for the city on the prescence of other mythical beasts.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHEN_07_BUTTON">
			<Text>It is good that this creature is around then!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_07_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A Zantonius Hamm is gracing our cities!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Northern: Banshee-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_08">
			<Text>Banshee</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_08_DESC">
			<Text>The wails of an otherworldly being are being heard across our empire! Those who hear the cry of the spectral Banshee believe that a member of their family is fated to die within a short time. Families across the empire have taken to huddling inside their houses in areas where the wail have been heard, and the few brave enough to venture out at night claim that the spirit appears like a beautiful woman dressed in white, or as a hideously ugly old hag.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHEN_08_BUTTON">
			<Text>Plug your ears!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_08_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We plugged our ears so that the Banshee was rendered powerless!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Northern: Troll-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_09">
			<Text>Troll</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_09_DESC">
			<Text>Old folk stories are starting to unnerve our subjects. They speak of fierce, humanoid monsters that rampage during the night, but hide during the day, in fear of sunlight. These creatures vary in size from that of a man and a mountain, and have skins like trees or rocks. They live in the forests, or mountains, or under bridges; in other words everywhere rural. The monsters devour goats, sheep, cows and men alike, and threaten our very existance. Our citizens call them trolls. What ever shall we do?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHEN_09_BUTTON">
			<Text>Send out troops to investigate these monsters.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_09_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Our troops did not return. We hope they just got lost. *Shifty eyes*</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Northern: Leprechaun -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_10">
			<Text>Leprechaun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_10_DESC">
			<Text>There have been reports of a little bearded man in your empire, a leprechaun. He is described as wearing a coat and hat. The leprechaun is said to have a hidden pot of gold at the end of the rainbow. People say if this leprechaun is captured by humans, he will grant three wishes in exchange for his freedom.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHEN_10_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us find and capture this little man!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_NORTHERN_10_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The capture of a Leprechaun is sure to lead to great riches!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--OCEANIC-->
		<!--Wayfinders-->
		<Delete Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_OCEANIC" />
		<Delete Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_OCEANIC_DESC" />
		<Delete Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_OCEANIC_OUTCOME_1" />
		<Delete Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_OCEANIC_OUTCOME_RESULT_1" />
		<Delete Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_OCEANIC_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION" />
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_OCEANIC">
			<Text>Wayfinders</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_OCEANIC_DESC">
			<Text>
				The waves on the horizon speak of unseen islands beyond.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_OCEANIC_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>We shall follow Mauis Hook until it draws up new lands.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_OCEANIC_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive a free Settler which can embark across Oceans and which gains additional Sight. This unit may only found a city on a foreign continent[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_OCEANIC_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have been inspired to seek out unknown lands beyond the seas.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Oceanic: Pouakai-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_01">
			<Text>Pouakai</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_01_DESC">
			<Text>"Right before my eyes!" the blustered warrior spat, "It just swooped from the skies and devoured him in one swift gulp!" He referred, of course, to the monstrous Pouakai; a beast of the air with wings the size of several men, and a hunger to match. We cannot rest easy whilst this beast casts over our heads a blanket of fear, but no mere man is match for this monster. We must pray to the Gods for help.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>The Gods will hear us!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have prayed to the Gods to aide us in our fight against the Pouakai, and behold; they have answered!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Oceanic: Taniwha-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_02">
			<Text>Taniwha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_02_DESC">
			<Text>Deep amidst the jungles and beneath the deepest of waters, where the waves swallow men whole and the caves are filled with perpetual darkness, lies the old and wise Taniwha. Recently, a warrior from {1_CityName} returned with a claim of having met with one of these ancient creatures, and having learned of the secrets to counting. We must set out and drink of this Taniwha's knowledge, and if we are unworthy, let it devour us with no remorse.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>We shall find this Taniwha!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have encountered a Taniwha; we shared a bit of lunch, and then gained its wise knowledge!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Oceanic: Huaka'i po-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_03">
			<Text>Huaka'i po</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_03_DESC">
			<Text>Visitors to our sacred sites and battlefields claim to have seen the ghosts of our fallen warriors marching from their graves to these places. It is said that unless an ancestor is among their ranks, those who witness this procession are doomed to die. That is unless, of course, one strips off all their clothes and lies naked on the ground. What should we do about these stories?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us lie down naked to protect our families!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Stripping naked brings great tidings upon our empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Oceanic: Te Wheke-a-Muturangi-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_04">
			<Text>Te Wheke-a-Muturangi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_04_DESC">
			<Text>Some of our fishermen from *city* have been complaining of dwindling catches. They say that a creature, much like a giant octopus, has been stealing the fish from their hooks. When they try to pull in the catch, they are left with hooks coated in the creature's slime. Because the creature threatens their livelihoods, the fishermen demand that we do something about the beast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>Find it and kill it!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_OCEANIC_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The terrible Te Wheke-a-Muturangi is no more!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ORIENTAL-->
		<!--Warrior's Service-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ORIENTAL">
			<Text>Warrior's Service</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ORIENTAL_DESC">
			<Text>
				A noble warrior from an honoured family has pledged their life to our service. They would have us be their master, and we would have them be our honour-bound servant.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ORIENTAL_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>I'm not interested.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ORIENTAL_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>Very well. I shall accept this pledge of fealty.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ORIENTAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_ORIENTAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain a free high-level Military unit[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_ORIENTAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have turned away a noble warrior who had pledged their life to our protection.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_ORIENTAL_OUTCOME_RESULT_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have accepted the service of a noble warrior who has pledged their life to our protection.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_ORIENTAL">
			<Text>A noble warrior has been enlisted into the protection of {1_LeaderName} of {2_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ORIENTAL: Fenghuang-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_01">
			<Text>Fenghuang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_01_DESC">
			<Text>The Fenghuang is the lord of all birds. Her body is a visage of the cosmos: her head the sky, her eyes the sun, her back the moon, her feet the earth, and her tail the planets. We honour this creature as the female to the male dragon; the yin to its yang.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We honour this magnificant creature.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have honoured the Fenghuang; the magnificant lord of all birds.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ORIENTAL: Qilin-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_02">
			<Text>Qilin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_02_DESC">
			<Text>We could not believe our eyes. A glimpse of the legendary Qilin - a dragon possessing of antlers and of skin laced with fire - is said to only appear before those of sage-like quality; portending either their end, or their further enlightenment.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>This is surely a good sign.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have witnissed of the legendary Qilin; a sign of our enlightenment.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ORIENTAL: Stunfisk-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_03">
			<Text>Stunfisk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_03_DESC">
			<Text>A wild Stunfisk has appeared! This magnificant creature is said to appear as a flounder with the means of transmitting electricity to any unsuspecting traveller who would step upon it. This is surely the most powerful creature in all the world.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>We must capture it and breed it with a Wailord.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have captured the legendary Stunfisk. Now to dump it in a PC.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ORIENTAL: Mogwai-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_04">
			<Text>Mogwai</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_04_DESC">
			<Text>Travelling merchants are said to be peddling small, furry creatures called Mogwai among their wares. The little animals are said to be extremely cute and cuddly, but the instructions given to those who buy these creatures by the merchant are often too difficult for them to follow. If these Mogwai receive food after midnight, or interact with liquid water in any way, they spawn hideous little gremlin creatures capable of great damage for their size.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>Of course! We are not ready!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Disaster has been averted, for we have shied away from the treacherous Mogwai.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ORIENTAL: Godzilla-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_05">
			<Text>Godzilla</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_05_DESC">
			<Text>A fishing boat off our coast, the Eiko Maru, has been devastated by an unknown terror from the deep. When asked what attacked his boat and killed his crew, the captain repeats only a single word: "Gojira." Fishermen at several other villages have also heard of this beast, calling it the King of the Monsters and leading us to a gigantic trail of footprints. The locals say the monster has a terrifying roar and can breath a beam of fire from its mouth that destroys anything it touches!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_05_BUTTON">
			<Text>Trap it on an uninhabited island and keep it there!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_05_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Godzilla shall never ruin our day!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ORIENTAL: Yuki-onna-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_06">
			<Text>Yuki-onna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_06_DESC">
			<Text>In the colder parts of your empire, travelers are said to have been found frozen to death during snowstorms. The locals blame the Yuki-onna, a beautiful pale woman who is actually a ghost. She may or may not be nude!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_06_BUTTON">
			<Text>We must find this lovely woman!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_06_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A nude ghost has been found to be nothing more than a filthy old hag that needs to shave her legs!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ORIENTAL: Jiangshi-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_07">
			<Text>Jiangshi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_07_DESC">
			<Text>There are reports of a horror in your lands, the Jiangshi! It is an undead being that moves about by hopping, with its arms outstretched. It is said to kill living beings by absorbing their life force during the night. In daytime, it sleeps in a coffin or a cave.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_07_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us find this hopping horror and destroy it!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_07_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Our quest for the deadly Jiangshi revealed the best to be nothing more than a friendly Hoppip!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ORIENTAL: Kitsune-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_08">
			<Text>Kitsune</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_08_DESC">
			<Text>There are reports of a being called the kitsune! This kitsune may look like a fox, but it can change form into a human, often an attractive woman. It uses this to trick humans. Some of our citizens suspect their wives of secretly being kitsune!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_08_BUTTON">
			<Text>Search all the households for these foxy ladies!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_ORIENTAL_08_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Although we could not find the kitsune, we did inspire a generation of new artists!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--PAPAL-->
		<!--Political Philosopher-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_PAPAL">
			<Text>Political Philosopher</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_PAPAL_DESC">
			<Text>
				A philosopher particularly adept at political discourse has arrived at our court. But perhaps his teachings are too radical for our nation.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_PAPAL_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>Send him and his nonsense ideas away!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_PAPAL_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_PAPAL_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have turned from our court a talented political philosopher.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_PAPAL_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>We welcome him most warmly.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_PAPAL_OUTCOME_2_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain a free Great Writer[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_PAPAL_OUTCOME_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have accepted into our court a talented political philosopher.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Papal: Gargoyle-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_01">
			<Text>Gargoyle</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_01_DESC">
			<Text>Statues in the city of {1_City} have reportedly been seen as coming to live in the dead of night and clambering around people's rooftops. These statues were built to ward off evil, but it appears that some might be the harbingers of evil themselves!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We shall have these statues dismantled.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have dismantled the statues of Gargoyles reportedly coming to live in the dead of night.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Papal: Monaciello-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_02">
			<Text>Monaciello</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_02_DESC">
			<Text>Citizens have reported seeing the visage of an elderly man dressed in the garments of a monk and a broad brimmed hat along the road to {1_City}. They allege the man, affectionately called 'Monaciello' - the little Monk to be a beneficient spirit that helps travelers in need.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Then we shall declare this man a guardian of travelers-by.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have declared an elderly man a guardian of the roads.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Papal: Atheist-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_03">
			<Text>Atheist</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_03_DESC">
			<Text>Some men from a foreign land have taken lodging in the city of {1_City}, where they rant that "God is dead" or even subvert the very existence of God!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Then they do not belong in this holy city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_PAPAL_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have exiled a band of men who claim that God does not exist.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--POLAR-->
		<!--Circumpolar Council-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_POLAR">
			<Text>Circumpolar Council</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_POLAR_DESC">
			<Text>The great peoples of the cold regions have come together to discuss matters concerning all. They have invited us to speak on behalf of the {1_CivAdj} people, and to serve their interest.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_POLAR_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>We shall take part, naturally.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_POLAR_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All cities begin celebrating 'We Love the King Day' for 5 turns[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_POLAR_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have taken part in the Circumpolar Council.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_POLAR_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>We are a unique people. We must abstaina and reject this council.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_POLAR_OUTCOME_2_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_POLAR_OUTCOME_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have decline to take part in the Circumpolar Council.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Polar: Apara-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_POLAR_01">
			<Text>Apara</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_POLAR_01_DESC">
			<Text>People in {1_City} have reported the sighting of an Apara - the ghost of a boy murdered in cold blood. They allege that the ghost will only depart once his killer has been found.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_POLAR_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>Then we must launch an investigation into the murder.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_POLAR_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have captured the criminal responsible for the murder of a local boy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--SAHUL-->
		<!--Ceremony-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL">
			<Text>Ceremony</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL_DESC">
			<Text>The time has come for our nation to host a ceremony. But what sort of ceremony remains to be decided.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>We shall host a corroboree to honour the ancestral creators.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Celebrations begin in honour of the ancestral creators.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>We shall host a kulaw gudpuday to honour those have recently departed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL_OUTCOME_2_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All cities begin celebrating 'We Love the King Day' for 5 turns[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL_OUTCOME_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Celebrations begin in honour of the recently depareted.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL_OUTCOME_3">
			<Text>We shall host a sing-sing to celebrate peace among our people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL_OUTCOME_3_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SAHUL_OUTCOME_3_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Celebrations begin in honour of peace amongst our people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Sahul: Bunyip-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SAHUL_01">
			<Text>Bunyip</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SAHUL_01_DESC">
			<Text>A hunting band from {1_City} have been said to have killed a Bunyip - a water creature with the characteristics of a duck, a crocodile, and a walrus. The Bunyip had allegedly been picking off local fishermen that had gotten too close to the river in which it had made its home.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SAHUL_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>This is good to hear.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SAHUL_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Local fishermen have killed a Bunyip said to have been haunting a local fishing spot.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Sahul: Bulugu-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SAHUL_02">
			<Text>Bulugu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SAHUL_02_DESC">
			<Text>The wife to a local chief in {1_City} has reportedly been kidnapped by what the locals refer to as a Bulugu - a serpentine but human-like creature. The chief has asked us to assist him in recovering his wife.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SAHUL_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>We must show that acts such as these are not tolerated.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SAHUL_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have successfully recovered the wife to a local chief kidnapped by a Bulugu.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--SEMITIC-->
		<!--Chosen people-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SEMITIC">
			<Text>Chosen people</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SEMITIC_DESC">
			<Text>
				A divine voice has elected of a land that we are destined to settle. We, as chosen people, must oblige.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SEMITIC_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>And so we shall oblige.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SEMITIC_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain a free Settler and a free Worker[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SEMITIC_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have been chosen to settle a faraway land.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_SEMITIC">
			<Text>The {1_Adj} people have been chosen to settle a faraway land.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Semitic: Golem-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SEMITIC_01">
			<Text>Golem</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SEMITIC_01_DESC">
			<Text>We have heard reports of a strange happening in a village near {1_CityName}. A local rabbi and the followers of his faith, beset by attacks from a hateful mob, has conjured a Golem in defense of his temple. The Golem was brought to life with bricks and clay, and defended the temple until the mob withdrew. The story has spread throughout the nation, and our people are looking to it as a source of comfort as they practice their beliefs in sometimes violent discrimination.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SEMITIC_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>This story should serve as caution to the intolerant.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SEMITIC_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have endorsed a story about a conjured Golem defending a religious minority.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Semitic: Natan-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SEMITIC_02">
			<Text>Natan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SEMITIC_02_DESC">
			<Text>"Why this?" "Why that?" "Why me? "Why you?" bellows from the dark of a {1_CityName} night, "Why not this? Why not that? Why not Israel? Or two? Or three? Or the Vandals?" It is the sardonic cry of the Natan - that which is said to drive any being into madness. It would be a far greater mercy to have {1_CityName} razed to the ground, than to bear the home of this strange creature.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SEMITIC_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>At least we know where not to travel!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SEMITIC_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Upon reflection, that the location of the Natan is known will better prepare us to avoid it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--SOUTHERN-->
		<!--Political Philosopher-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SOUTHERN">
			<Text>Political Philosopher</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SOUTHERN_DESC">
			<Text>A philosopher particularly adept at political discourse has arrived at our court. But perhaps his teachings are too radical for our nation.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SOUTHERN_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>Send him and his nonsense ideas away!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SOUTHERN_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain {1_Num} [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SOUTHERN_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have turned from our court a talented political philosopher.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SOUTHERN_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>We welcome him most warmly.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SOUTHERN_OUTCOME_2_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain a free Great Writer[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_SOUTHERN_OUTCOME_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have accepted into our court a talented political philosopher.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Southern: Gargoyle-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SOUTHERN_01">
			<Text>Gargoyle</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SOUTHERN_01_DESC">
			<Text>Statues in the city of {1_City} have reportedly been seen as coming to life in the dead of night and clambering around people's rooftops. These statues were built to ward off evil, but it appears that some might be the harbingers of evil themselves!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SOUTHERN_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We shall have these statues dismantled.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SOUTHERN_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have dismantled the statues of Gargoyles reportedly coming to live in the dead of night.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Southern: Monaciello-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SOUTHERN_02">
			<Text>Monaciello</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SOUTHERN_02_DESC">
			<Text>Citizens have reported seeing the visage of an elderly man dressed in the garments of a monk and a broad brimmed hat along the road to {1_City}. They allege the man, affectionately called 'Monaciello' - the little Monk to be a beneficient spirit that helps travelers in need.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SOUTHERN_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Then we shall declare this man a guardian of travelers-by.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_SOUTHERN_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have declared an elderly man a guardian of the roads.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--STEPPE-->
		<!-- Great Horde -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_STEPPE">
			<Text>Great Horde</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_STEPPE_DESC">
			<Text>
				In our time of war, a great horde has rallied to our cause. Our nomadic brothers rise up in unison to join us in our glorious onslaught of the enemy.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_STEPPE_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>This will surely favour our victory.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_STEPPE_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive 3 free sources of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]A Great Horde appears[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_STEPPE_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A great horde has rallied to our cause.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_STEPPE">
			<Text>A great {1_CivAdjective} horde has ralled to the cause of {2_LeaderName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Steppe: Death Worm-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_01">
			<Text>Death Worm</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_01_DESC">
			<Text>A soldier came stumbling into our tent one late night, flustered and out of breath. "A worm!" he cried, "As big as a horse and red as blood! I barely escaped with my life." He spoke of the great Death Worm; a monstrous beast which spewed acid; a beast which could kill a human with a mere touch. We must move on from this place, and be thankful that the soldier is still alive.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We must be thankful.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We are thankful that one of our soldiers survived an encounter with the great Death Worm.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Steppe: Death Worm-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_02">
			<Text>Death Worm</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_02_DESC">
			<Text>The people who inhabit the desert regions of our empire have begun to fear a burrowing creature that is reportedly red and several feet long. Nomads who claim to have survived encounters with this "death worm" claim it can kill from a distance, either from spitting poison or by electrocution; a few claim that just touching the worm is certain death. Its poison is powerful enough to eat through even the steel of our swords!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>Shocking! Let us find these worms!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have not found a trace of this so-called "death worm," which is surely cause for rejoice.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Steppe: Hortdan-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_03">
			<Text>Hortdan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_03_DESC">
			<Text>Tales of a bloodthirsty spirit have begun to circulate through the empire. In addition to its taste for blood, the creature is said to be able to turn invisible and transform into any animal it wishes. According to the few who are brave enough to track sightings of the creature, it is also apparently immortal, sustaining itself on the lifeblood of our citizens!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Find its weakness!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_STEPPE_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The Hortdan shall not last long whilst I'm around!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--TOTALITARIAN-->
		<!--Celebrations For Our Glorious Leader-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_TOLTALITARIAN">
			<Text>Celebrations For Our Glorious Leader</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_TOLTALITARIAN_DESC">
			<Text>
				Spontaneously, and absolutely not under any duress whatsoever, the people have begun celebrating their love for their Glorious Leader - you! The celebrations begin with the customary weeping of children in honour of our heroic heroism and glory, and, as usual, will end in the honourary relay race between our loving soldiers and our ensla-also loving and completely free citizens. Hooray for you![NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_TOLTALITARIAN_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>I'm positively flattered!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_TOLTALITARIAN_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>Not good enough! Execute everyone!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_TOLTALITARIAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All current Land Units gain +1 [ICON_MOVES] Movement[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All cities with a garrison begin celebrating 'We Love the King Day' for 2 turns[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_TOLTALITARIAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET]All cities lose most of their [ICON_CITIZEN] Population[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]...[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_TOLTALITARIAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have been humbled by our people's endearing love for us - we had no idea!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_TOLTALITARIAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have executed everyone nonchalantly. All those buildings that suddenly appeared - they're graveyards. Hope you're happy. Hitler.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_TOLTALITARIAN">
			<Text>People are celebrating their undying love for their glorious leader of {1_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Totalitarian: Democracy-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TOTALITARIAN_01">
			<Text>Democracy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TOTALITARIAN_01_DESC">
			<Text>Ancient documents telling of a political process which allows the people to participate in government have been uncovered. They call this strange manifestation: "Democracy," literally 'rule of the people.' Of course, as a sensible and most gracious dictator, we should have these documents executed immediately.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TOTALITARIAN_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>What utter gobwash! These documents must be destroyed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TOTALITARIAN_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have destroyed all documents pertaining to this thing called "Democracy."</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--TRIBAL AMERICAN-->
		<!--War Chief-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_TRIBAL_AMERICAN">
			<Text>War Chief</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_DESC">
			<Text>
				A vision of the Great Spirit has befallen one of our tribesmen. With this vision, a great war chief has been elected to lead us to military triumph.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>We are honoured by the Great Spirit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive a free Great General[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>One of our tribesman has become a great war chief to our people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_TRIBAL_AMERICAN">
			<Text>A great War Chief has been anointed amongst in the {1_Adj} nation.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--TribalAmerican: Underwater Panther-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_01">
			<Text>Underwater Panther</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_01_DESC">
			<Text>By offering his best tobacco, a trader from {1_City} has struck a bargain with the Underwater Panther. The great cat will no longer capsize our vessels with its horns, or churn the waters with its serpentine tail, or scare away our fish with its torrential roar. We may now fish and mine along our waterways without fear of such misfortunes.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>Our people can now swim without a fear.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A deal has been struck with the beastly Underwater Panther.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--TribalAmerican: Rokita-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_02">
			<Text>Stone Giant</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_02_DESC">
			<Text>While tracking through the northern wilds, a hunter chanced upon a beguiling, though gigantic, woman. She enticed him back to her home, but before their affair could be accomplish, they were discovered by her husband - equally gigantic and clad in stone armor. Thanks to his quick wit and quicker feet, the hunter managed to escape the lumbering giant, taking the creatures enchanted as as a prize.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>This is cause for celebration!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A Stone Giant has been captured by one of our kin. Let's hope it doesn't complain about seagulls!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--TribalAmerican: Horned Serpent-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_03">
			<Text>Horned Serpent</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_03_DESC">
			<Text>A medicine man has delved into the deep caverns near {1_City} and slain a monstrous rattlesnake with iridescent scales and antlers to shame to noblest elk. Though only the offspring of the chaotic spirit that dwells Below, this Horned Serpent had caused all manner of havoc and pestilence in the area. Now that it is dead, the jeweled scale has been plucked from its brow and the future has been revealed to us.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>I foresee the dawning of a glorious new era!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The slaughter of a Horned Serpent bodes well for our future.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--TribalAmerican: Thunderbird-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_04">
			<Text>Thunderbird</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_04_DESC">
			<Text>Donning the form of a mighty eagle, one of the Thunderers has descended from Above. With wings that stir the winds and eyes that flash lightning, he has vanquished the monsters that have befouled our lands. As his reward, he has chosen a woman from {1_City} to be his bride.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let's celebrate the union of earth and heavens!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We celebrate the coming of the magnificent Thunderbird.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--TribalAmerican: Thunderbird-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_05">
			<Text>Wendigo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_05_DESC">
			<Text>Several tribal elders have come to us with claims that the stories of the Wendigo are true. They claim that during the unusually harsh winter we just endured that several who could not cope with the hardship turned to cannibalism. The elders claim that they ran across the slaughtered remains of a few unlucky enough to have travelled alone, and say that the footprints around the bodies have grown according to the amount of meat they've eaten. They wish us to deal with the beast before more or killed, or another turns into a Wendigo.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_05_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us find this beast!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_TRIBAL_AMERICAN_05_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The Wendigo shall not bother us anymore.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--WEST AFRICAN-->
		<!--Precious Luxury-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_WEST_AFRICAN">
			<Text>Precious Luxury</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_WEST_AFRICAN_DESC">
			<Text>
				A precious source of {1_Luxury} has been discovered near the city of {2_City}! For our enduring faith and wisdom, we have surely been blessed with this gift of wealth.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_WEST_AFRICAN_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>This is excellent news.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_WEST_AFRICAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]A source of {1_Luxury} is found near the city of {2_City}[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_WEST_AFRICAN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have discovered a new source of {1_Luxury} near the city of {2_City}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_WEST_AFRICAN">
			<Text>A rich source of {1_Luxury} has been found near the {2_Adj} city of {3_CityName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--WestAfrican: Mokele-mbembe-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_01">
			<Text>Mokele-mbembe</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_01_DESC">
			<Text>A fisherman in the city of {1_CityName} has brought back the tooth of the legendary Mokele-mbembe; a monstrous lizard said to live at the basin of a nearby river. This is the first piece of evidence that we have which prooves the existence of this beast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A joyous occassion to behold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>We can breathe a sigh of relief.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--WestAfrican: Ghabali-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_02">
			<Text>Ghabali</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_02_DESC">
			<Text>Villagers who live close to the river outside {1_CityName} claim that a giant animal has been attacking people. They say the creature looks like a crocodile, but is much larger, and stands upright on its legs. They claim that the creature has terrorized their river for generations, and that they have even caught and eaten it!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Bring me its skull!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>The skull of the Ghabali shall make a fine crown.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--WestAfrican: Asanbosam-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_03">
			<Text>Asanbosam</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_03_DESC">
			<Text>There are tales of a creature called the Asanbosam living in the forests of our empire. It is said to live in the trees and has iron teeth and iron hook feet. This beast feasts on unsuspecting humans on the ground below!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Let us search the trees for this monstrosity!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WEST_AFRICAN_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>Searching for the Asanbosam has proven that the beast was nothing more than a Sudowoodo!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--WESTERN-->
		<!--Colonial Investors-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_WESTERN">
			<Text>Colonial Investors</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_WESTERN_DESC">
			<Text>A wealthy entrepreneur has approached us with a petition to allow the establishment of a trading colony in a far off land. In exchange for our patent, funds would be provided to cover the expenses of such an endeavour, although we would be expected to provide for security.[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_WESTERN_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>We give our assent to this venture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_WESTERN_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>There shall be no new colony.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_WESTERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1">
			<Text>[COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT][ICON_BULLET]Lose {2_Num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Receive a free Settler and {1_Num} [ICON_GOLD] Gold[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_JFD_WESTERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_2">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Nothing[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_WESTERN_OUTCOME_RESULT_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have given assent to the creation of a new settlement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Western: Mermaid-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN">
			<Text>Mermaid</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_01_DESC">
			<Text>Recently, a scientist has claimed to have found the remnants of a mermaid's body! It bears a remarkable resemblance to a fish and an ape being sown together by an amateur, but nevertheless, it seems like concrete proof they exist. What do you make of this, m'lord/lady?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_01_BUTTON">
			<Text>This is obvisouly cause for celebration!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_01_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have obviously - obviously - found evidence of the existence of mermaids.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Western: Giant-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_02">
			<Text>Giant</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_02_DESC">
			<Text>It has been said that a giant has been captured and slain near the city of {1_CityName}. The giant had been for decades terrorising local farms; stealing crops and livestock, but now the people of {1_CityName} can rest easy in the knowledge of its death.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_02_BUTTON">
			<Text>We honour the heroes whom slew this monster.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_02_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have indulged in the wisdom of a sailor who claims to have killed a Kraken.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Western: Dragon-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_03">
			<Text>Dragon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_03_DESC">
			<Text>An alchemist has approached us with a strange offer: "Tis' the blood of a dragon fer m'lord," he says to us. The blood of a dragon is a rare commodity; said to contain magical substances which can cure of any ailment. A most valuable medicine to have in our stock.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_03_BUTTON">
			<Text>We shall certainly want this medicine to study.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_03_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have accepted the purchase of what an alchemist claims to be dragon blood.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Western: The Doctor-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_04">
			<Text>The Doctor</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_04_DESC">
			<Text>A mysterious man has been seen in several of our villages, often in the company of a young woman. The pair are observed for several days or weeks in a single location before they disappear, only to pop up elsewhere. Some say that they use a big blue box to travel between destinations or even in time, and call this stranger "the Doctor." Such a madman in a box who could appear anywhere without warning could be dangerous to our empire. Should we trace his movements?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_04_BUTTON">
			<Text>That would be quite a show!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_04_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have resolved to track down the mysertious "Doctor."</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Western: Globster-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_05">
			<Text>Globster</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_05_DESC">
			<Text>An unidentified corpse has washed up on our shores. It resembles a mass of boneless flesh, and the locals have begun to call the creature a "globster." The sudden appearance of a creature this size is unsettling and may represent the vanguard of an unknown terror from the deep.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_05_BUTTON">
			<Text>Poke it with a stick!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_05_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>We have pocked a disturbing, gelatinous blob with a stick, triggering a Golden Age!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Western: Barghest-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_06">
			<Text>Barghest</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_06_DESC">
			<Text>Hikers and joggers on our roads have begun to report a creature that they describe to look like a large, black dog with glowing red eyes. It is said to have monstrous teeth and claws, and can turn invisible, though one can hear the sound of chains as it moves. It has been sighted laying across the doorstep of houses, heralding the impending death of one of the people living there, or leading a funeral procession of all the dogs in that town. </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_06_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us find this beast to calm our citizens!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_06_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>No more Barghests shall haunt our people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Western: Tarasque-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_07">
			<Text>Tarasque</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_07_DESC">
			<Text>There are reports of a monster devastating the landscape surrounding the city of {1_City}. It is called the tarasque and possesses a lions head, six short legs, an ox-like body covered with a turtle shell, and a scaly tail that ends in a scorpions sting. The locals are terrified of it. However, a certain holy woman claims she possesses the power to tame the beast, but she requires some of our soldiers to protect her in case her abilities fail.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_07_BUTTON">
			<Text>Let us find this beast to calm our citizens!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_MYTH_WESTERN_07_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The aide of a holy woman has allowed us to tame the Tarasque. It shall now live out its days in a small, glass fishbowl.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>