<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 3/17/2015 4:02:18 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!--CONCEPTS-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SLAVERY_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Slavery: Introduction</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SLAVERY_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Slavery[ENDCOLOR] is one of the new gameplay elements added by Cities in Development. It is a method of purchasing Military Units outright. These Units are often very cheap, however, they earn only 50% of the normal XP from combat. They also cost much more to upgrade.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You cannot enslave Mechanized Units such as Tanks, Naval Units, Siege Units, or Air Units, however. You must buy these with Gold instead if you wish to rush them.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SLAVERY_SHACKLES_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Slavery: Acquiring Shackles</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SLAVERY_SHACKLES_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Shackles[ENDCOLOR] are the new Strategic Resource used to 'enslave' Military Units. They can be acquired from four sources:[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Capturing Barbarian Encampments.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Capturing Civilian Units.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]'Enslaving' enemy Cities.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Trading with Puppeted and Occupied Cities.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Trading with Militaristic City-States.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--BELIEFS-->
		<!--God of War-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_JFD_GOD_WAR_SHORT_DESC">
			<Text>God of War</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_JFD_GOD_WAR_DESC">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_JFD_SHACKLES] from clearing Encampments and capturing Civilians</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Human Sacrifices-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_JFD_HUMAN_SACRIFICES_SHORT_DESC">
			<Text>Human Sacrifices</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--BUILDINGS-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_PYRAMID_HELP">
			<Text>Tile improvement construction speed increased by 25% and two Peasants appear near the City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--IMPROVEMENTS-->
		<!--Village-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_VILLAGE">
			<Text>Construct a Village</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--POLICIES-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_JFD_CITIZENSHIP_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Citizenship[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]Tile improvement construction rate increased by 25% and a Peasant appears near the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--PROMOTIONS-->
		<!--Enslaved-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_ENSLAVED">
			<Text>Enslaved</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_ENSLAVED_HELP">
			<Text>An [ICON_JFD_SHACKLES] Enslaved Unit earns 50% less XP and costs 100% more to upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Upgrade Discount-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_UPGRADE_DISCOUNT">
			<Text>Upgrade Discount</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_UPGRADE_DISCOUNT_HELP">
			<Text>-50% [ICON_GOLD] cost to upgrade into a Worker.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--PROCESSES-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROCESS_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS">
			<Text>Declaration of Human Rights</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROCESS_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_HELP">
			<Text>Contribute this city's [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards the Declaration of Human Rights project.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--RESOLUTIONS-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOLUTION_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS">
			<Text>Declaration of Human Rights</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOLUTION_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_HELP">
			<Text>Begins the Declaration of Human Rights project. Once underway, Civilizations can contribute [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards its completion by selecting it in the city production list.  When complete, Civilizations receive bonuses based on how much they contributed.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_TROPHY_GOLD]: {TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_REWARD_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_3_HELP}[NEWLINE][ICON_TROPHY_SILVER]: {TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_REWARD_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_2_HELP}[NEWLINE][ICON_TROPHY_BRONZE]: {TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_REWARD_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_1_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Available once any Civilization discovers Industrialization.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS">
			<Text>Declaration of Human Rights</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_SPLASH">
			<Text>Leaders from around the world have gathered to observe the creation of an International Criminal Court. As the world watches, Civilizations pledge their support to the cause and pursuit of a universal justice.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_REWARD_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_1">
			<Text>Observing Member</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_REWARD_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_1_HELP">
			<Text>Forbids [ICON_JFD_SHACKLES] Slavery from all sources. +3 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_REWARD_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_2">
			<Text>Signatory Member</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_REWARD_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_2_HELP">
			<Text>Forbids [ICON_JFD_SHACKLES] Slavery from all sources. +5 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_REWARD_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_3">
			<Text>Hosting Member</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEAGUE_PROJECT_REWARD_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_3_HELP">
			<Text>Forbids [ICON_JFD_SHACKLES] Slavery from all sources. +10 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_1_DESC">
			<Text>JFD: Human Rights Bronze</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_2_DESC">
			<Text>JFD: Human Rights Silver</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HUMAN_RIGHTS_3_DESC">
			<Text>JFD: Human Rights Gold</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--RESOURCES-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_JFD_SHACKLES">
			<Text>Shackles</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_JFD_SHACKLES_TEXT">
			<Text>Slavery is a system whereby some people are judged far inferior to others and are treated as objects or possessions, with no more rights than those afforded to chairs or cattle. Slavery has existed as long as human history, from earliest primitive times to the enlightened days of Greece and Rome and right up until today. Sometimes convicted criminals were made into slaves. Sometimes captured enemies of the state were enslaved. Sometimes people of a specific race or coloration were enslaved. In some civilizations a person could purchase their freedom or were allotted it after being enslaved for a specific period of time.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The advantage of slavery is that it allows people to be forced to do jobs that they would otherwise refuse to do without adequate compensation. Cheap labor results in concentration of wealth and thus the creation of great buildings and temples or the maintenance of large professional armies. Aside from its basic moral repugnance, the disadvantages of slavery are numerous; it corrupts both slave and master, it badly underutilizes the intelligence and creativity of the subject people, and it almost inevitably leads to revolts and internal strife.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_JFD_SHACKLES_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<!--UNITS-->
		<!--Peasant-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_PEASANT">
			<Text>Peasant</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_PEASANT_HELP">
			<Text>Improves [ICON_FOOD] Food [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold by constructing Improvements on map tiles outside of Cities at a slower rate than Workers and Slaves. Cannot build Railroads.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_PEASANT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Peasant constructs roads and builds improvements like farms and mines. It cannot defend itself, so accompany it with a military unit when it is in dangerous territory. The Peasant works at a slower rate than a Worker or Slave and cannot build Railroads.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_PEASANT_PEDIA">
			<Text>A peasant is a member of a traditional class of farmers, either laborers or owners of small farms, especially in the Middle Ages under feudalism, or more generally, in any pre-industrial society. Peasants either hold title to land in fee simple, or hold land by any of several forms of land tenure, among them socage, quit-rent, leasehold, and copyhold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Slave-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_SLAVE">
			<Text>Slave</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_JFD_SLAVE">
			<Text>Improves [ICON_FOOD] Food [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold by constructing Improvements on map tiles outside of Cities at a faster rate than Peasants. Can build Slave Plantations, but not Roads nor Railroads. Cannot repair Improvements.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May be expended to hurry [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_SLAVE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Slave builds improvements like farms and mines. It cannot defend itself, so accompany it with a military unit when it is in dangerous territory. It is faster than the Peasant, however, it cannot construct roads or railroads and cannot repair improvements. The Slave can also hurry production of a unit, building or Wonder in a city. The Slave is expended when used in either of these ways.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_JFD_SLAVE_TEXT">
			<Text>Slavery is the state in which one person is under the complete control of another; literally that one person is the property of another and forced to serve without the right of pay or protest. Historically, slavery was lucrative in all societies in maintaining economic stability, with three quarters of the world's population estimated to be slaves at the beginning of the 19th century, but the life of a slave was wretched. Today, slavery is outlawed in every country, following the example of the British Empire in the late 18th century, but there are an estimated 27 million people still living as slaves today; often as debt slaves, indentured servants, sex slaves, or child soldiers.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Worker-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_WORKER">
			<Text>Worker</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_JFD_WORKER">
			<Text>Improves [ICON_FOOD] Food [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold by constructing Improvements on map tiles outside of Cities at a faster rate than Peasants or Slaves. Can build Villages.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_WORKER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Worker constructs roads, railroads and builds improvements like farms and mines. It cannot defend itself, so accompany it with a military unit when it is in dangerous territory. This unit costs additional Maintenance over the Peasant and Slave, but works much faster.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_JFD_WORKER_TEXT">
			<Text>To survive, a civilization needs skilled workers. They may be highly trained engineers, or civilians conscripted into labor, but someone has to dig the mines, plant the fields and pave the roads. Without these men and women, a civilization will stagnate and eventually fall prey to a more vigorous neighbor.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--WONDERS-->
		<!--Stone Town-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_STONE_TOWN">
			<Text>Stone Town</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_STONE_TOWN_HELP">
			<Text>Gains an additional [ICON_SWAP] Trade Route slot. +20% [ICON_JFD_SHACKLES] Shackles from [ICON_SWAP] Trade Routes to Puppeted and Occupied Cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_STONE_TOWN_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE]"The Europeans and Americans residing in the town of Zanzibar are either Government officials, independent merchants, or agents for a few great mercantile houses in Europe and America"[NEWLINE] - Henry Morton Stanley[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_STONE_TOWN_PEDIA">
			<Text>Stone Town is the old part of Zanzibar City, on the Tanzanian island of Zanzibar. It is believed the first stone construction in the area began during the period in which the Sultan of Oman ruled over Zanzibar in the 18th - 19th centuries. In 1863, the Sultan of Oman moved his capital to Zanzibar, and created a lush palace complex on the island in Stone Town, and spurred the island and Stone Town into a period of rapid development. A war of sucession following the reign of one of the sultans caused Zanzibar to become an independant sultanate from Oman, leading to more development of Stone Town.  </Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>