<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 3/17/2015 4:02:18 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!--CONCEPTS-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Introduction</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Sovereignty[ENDCOLOR] is the measurement of your ability to govern your civilization. Sovereignty is needed to pass Political Reforms, although it is not expended in doing so; simply, you will need a minimum amount of Sovereignty before you can pass a Political Reform.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Sovereignty is accumulated from a variety of sources, such as Wonders and Reforms, up to a max of 50% or 100%, depending upon your specific Reforms. In almost all cases, Sovereignty bonuses require that certain conditions be met in all cities, for instance, having a garrison in all cities. These, again, are dependent upon your specific Reforms.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_LEGITIMACY_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Legitimacy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_LEGITIMACY_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Legitimacies[ENDCOLOR] describe your right to rule, and are specific Reforms that will be your main source of Sovereignty. These require that a certain condition be met in all cities. For instance, the 'Might' legitimacy will grant a bonus in Sovereignty only when all cities have a garrison. Later, it is possible to exclude Colonies and Puppets from this requirement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_ANARCHY_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Anarchy Sentiment</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_ANARCHY_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Anarchy Sentiment[ENDCOLOR] is the representation of your people's extreme dislike for your government. It is increased by certain Reforms and by the Revolutionaries Faction.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When Anarchy Sentiment exceeds 100%, it will cause your civilization to enter Anarchy for 1 turn. At 200%, it will trigger 2 turns of Anarchy, at 300%, it will trigger 3 turns, and so on. During this time, your cities will not be able to produce any yields.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_FACTIONS_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Factions</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_FACTIONS_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Factions[ENDCOLOR] are the groups that compete for power in your government's Legislature. These Factions differ by Government, but all will decrease the Sovereignty required to pass reforms that they support. Conversely, they will increase the Sovereignty required to pass Reforms that they oppose. The amount is based upon their share of power in the Legislature.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Revolutionaries[ENDCOLOR] are a unique Faction present in all Governments. They are calculated from your Excess Unhappiness and will oppose ALL Reforms. In addition, they will increase Anarchy Sentiment.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_GOVERNMENT_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Government</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_GOVERNMENT_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>The [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Government[ENDCOLOR] is how you rule your civilization. Usually, this is as either a Monarchy or a Republic. The main difference between Governments is in how their Legislatures are composed. However, Governments also unlock a unique Decision each.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_LEGISLATURE_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Legislature</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_LEGISLATURE_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>The [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Legislature[ENDCOLOR] is the legal body of government. It is composed of Factions and plays an important part in influencing the Sovereignty required to pass Reforms.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Every 25 turns, the Legislature (if you have one) will be (re-)filled with these Factions. Each Faction will take a share of 100%, based upon certain criteria unique to them. The specific mechanics of this differ by Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_DICTATORSHIP_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Dictatorship</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_DICTATORSHIP_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Dictatorship[ENDCOLOR] is one of the Government types available in Rise to Power. It describes a system of personal government, wherein supreme power lies in an ideologue - be it one or many. It is only available once you have chosen an Ideology. It has two Legislatures: Military Junta, and One-Party Assembly, and reduces the Sovereignty gained from fulfilling Legitimacies.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Military Junta[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]The Military Junta is a single Faction that composes your Legislature entirely. It will support strong Military control and aggressive Foreign relations.[NEWLINE]--------[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Favoured[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]--------[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY]Right[ENDCOLOR] Government Reforms[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY]Right[ENDCOLOR] Foreign Reforms[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY]Right[ENDCOLOR] Military Reforms[NEWLINE]--------[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]One-Party Assembly[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]The One-Party Assembly is similarly a single Faction, but what this Faction supports depends upon your chosen Ideology. With Autocracy, this Assembly will support strong Government and Military control. With Freedom, it will support weak control on Law and Culture. With Order, it will support strong control over Industry and Economy.[NEWLINE]--------[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Favoured (Autocracy)[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]--------[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY]Right[ENDCOLOR] Government Reforms[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY]Right[ENDCOLOR] Military Reforms[NEWLINE]--------[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Favoured (Order)[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]--------[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY]Right[ENDCOLOR] Economic Reforms[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY]Right[ENDCOLOR] Industrial Reforms[NEWLINE]--------[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Favoured (Freedom)[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]--------[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY]Left[ENDCOLOR] Culture Reforms[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY]Left[ENDCOLOR] Legal Reforms[NEWLINE]--------</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_HOLY_ROME_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Holy Rome</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_HOLY_ROME_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>The [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Holy Roman Empire[ENDCOLOR] is one of the Government types available in Rise to Power. It describes a system of consensus government, wherein supreme power lies in an organization of states. It is only available once you have constructed the Hofburg Palace wonder. It has one Legislature: the Privilegium, and increases the power of Factions.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Privilegium[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]The Privilegium is composed of Electors corresponding to your City-State Allies (Privilegium Mauis) or Friends (Privilegium Minor). Each of these Factions will support and oppose specific Reforms, based on the Trait of their originating City-State. Militaristic Electors, for instance, will support a focus on Military Reforms. The power of these Factions is determined by their Population compared to the Population of all members of the Holy Roman Empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_MONARCHY_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Monarchy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_MONARCHY_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monarchy[ENDCOLOR] is one of the Government types available in Rise to Power. It describes a system of private government, wherein supreme power lies in a single ruler. It has two Legislatures: Aritoscracy, and Parliament, unlocks the Versailles wonder, and increases the Sovereignty value of fulfilling Legitimacies.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Aristocracy[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]The Aristocracy is composed of up to three Factions: Burghers, Clergy, and Nobles. Each of these Factions will support and oppose specific Reforms. The Clergy, for instance, will support strong control over Culture and will oppose strong control over Religion. The power of these Factions is determined by your highest yields.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Parliament[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]The Parliament is composed of up to four Factions: Conservatives, Liberal, Socialists, and either Communists (Order), Fascists (Autocracy), or Libertarians (Freedom), depending upon your dominant Ideology. Each of these Factions will support and oppose specific Reforms. The Liberals, for instance, will support weak control over Culture and will oppose strong control over it. The power of these Factions is determined by your lowest yields and by the number of specialists.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_REPUBLIC_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Republic</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_REPUBLIC_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Republic[ENDCOLOR] is one of the Government types available in Rise to Power. It describes a system of public government, wherein supreme power lies in a body of citizens. It has two Legislatures: Oligarchy, and Democracy, unlocks the Doge's Palace wonder, and reduces the time between passing Reforms.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Oligarchy[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]The Oligarchy is composed of up to six Factions: Civic, Populist, Mercantile, Industrialist, Military, and Religion. Each of these Factions will both support and oppose a specific Reform Branch. The Civic Faction, for instance, will support all Legal Reforms but will oppose all Religion Reforms. The power of these Factions is determined by the number of your National Wonders, Social Policy Branches, Domestic and International Trade Routes, (Major) Active Wars, and (Major) State Religion followers.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Later, when you have an Ideology, these Factions will be replaced with up to three Factions: Fanaticists, Progressives, and Radicalists. These Factions function as amalgamations of the previous six Factions.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Democracy[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]The Democracy is composed of up to two Factions: Nationalists and Popularists. Where the Nationalists support all Rightest and oppose all Leftest Reforms, the Popularists support all Leftest and oppose all Rightest Reforms. This is regardless of the Branch to which the Reform belongs. The power of these Factions is determined by your Happiness and Unhappiness.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_SHOGUNATE_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Shogunate</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_SHOGUNATE_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>The [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Shogunate[ENDCOLOR] is one of the Government types available in Rise to Power. It describes a system of tripartite government, wherein supreme power lies between the Emperor, the Shogun, and the Daimyo. It is only available once you have constructed the Himeji Castle wonder. It has two Legislatures: the Emperor, and the Daimyo, and increases the power of Factions.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]The Daimyo[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]The Oligarchy is composed of up to six Factions: Civic, Populist, Mercantile, Industrialist, Military, and Religion. Each of these Factions will both support and oppose a specific Reform Branch. The Civic Faction, for instance, will support all Legal Reforms but will oppose all Religion Reforms. The power of these Factions is determined by the number of your National Wonders, Social Policy Branches, Domestic and International Trade Routes, (Major) Active Wars, and (Major) State Religion followers.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Later, when you have an Ideology, these Factions will be replaced with up to three Factions: Fanaticists, Progressives, and Radicalists. These Factions function as amalgamations of the previous six Factions.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]The Emperor[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]The Emperor is composed of up to two Factions: Nationalists and Popularists. Where the Nationalists support all Rightest and oppose all Leftest Reforms, the Popularists support all Leftest and oppose all Rightest Reforms. This is regardless of the Branch to which the Reform belongs. The power of these Factions is determined by your Happiness and Unhappiness.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_THEOCRACY_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Theocracy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_THEOCRACY_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Theocracy[ENDCOLOR] is one of the Government types available in Rise to Power. It describes a system of semi-private government, wherein supreme power lies in the divine. It is only available once you have made a religion that you've founded your State Religion. It has two Legislatures: Autocephaly, and Ecumenism, unlocks the St. Peter's Basilica wonder, and increases your Maximum Sovereignty.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Autocephacly[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]In Autocephaly, the Legislature is composed of as many Factions as there are cities following your State Religion. Each of these Factions will support or oppose a specific Reform Branch depending upon whether their originating city has more Faith, Culture, Gold, or Science output. These interests can change each turn, and are always supportive of Left Reforms but opposed to Right Reforms.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Ecumenism[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]In Ecumenism, the Legislature is composed of as many Factions as there are followers of your State Religion. Each of these Factions will support or oppose a specific Reform Branch depending upon whether their originating city has more Faith, Culture, Gold, or Science output. These interests can change each turn, and are always supportive of Right Reforms but opposed to Left Reforms.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_REFORMS_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Political Reforms</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_REFORMS_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Political Reforms[ENDCOLOR] are the main feature of Sovereignty. They are similar to Social Policies, but in addition to providing some kind of bonus, they provide some kind of penalty. Reforms do not cost anything to pass, but they require a minimum amount of Sovereignty and there is a cooldown between passing them. This minimum Sovereignty is determined by the era in which the Reform is unlocked, as well by your Legislature.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Political Reforms are grouped into sets of three alignments: Left, Centre, and Right. Reforms in a single group are mutually exclusive. They also belong to specific Branches, such as Culture, Legal, and Religion, but these are not exclusive. Different Factions will support and oppose different Alignments and different Branches.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_PRIVY_COUNCIL_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Sovereignty: Privy Council</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY_PRIVY_COUNCIL_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>The [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Privy Council[ENDCOLOR] is your advisory body. It can be filled with Great People, providing long-term bonuses instead of the short-term ones that they are normally expended for.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--BUILDINGS-->
		<!--LEADERS-->
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_AUGUSTUS">
			<Text>Augustus</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_GENGHIS_KHAN">
			<Text>Temujin</Text>
		</Replace>
		<!--DECISIONS-->
		<!--Hold Ceremony-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_HOLD_CEREMONY">
			<Text>Hold {1_Name} Ceremony</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_HOLD_CEREMONY_DESC">
			<Text>In celebration of our auspicious ascension, we propose a ceremony, to which all citizens and subjects are welcome!
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Requirements:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must have a Government.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]May only be enacted once per game.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Costs:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]{2_Num} [ICON_GOLD] Gold.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]1 {3_ResourceDesc}.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]The Capital begins celebrating [ICON_JFD_WLTKD] 'We Love the King Day' for {4_Num} turns.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_HOLD_CEREMONY_ENACTED_DESC">
			<Text>In celebration of our auspicious ascension, we propose a ceremony, to which all citizens and subjects are welcome!
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]All cities begin celebrating [ICON_JFD_WLTKD] 'We Love the King Day.'
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENT_JFD_HOLD_CEREMONY">
			<Text>{1_PlayerName} has held their {2_CeremonyName} Ceremony to mark their assumption of rule over the {3_CivName}.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Exercise Royal Prerogative-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_ROYAL_PREROGATIVE">
			<Text>Exercise Royal Prerogative</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_ROYAL_PREROGATIVE_DESC">
			<Text>
				There are times, in spite of the will of government, that the sovereign must take action. In these times, the Royal Prerogative must be exercised for the good of the nation.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Requirements:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must be a Monarchy.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must have a Legislature.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]May only be enacted once per era.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Costs:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]4 [ICON_MAGISTRATES] Magistrates.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Current [ICON_JFD_REFORM_COOLDOWN] Reform Cooldown is halved.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_ROYAL_PREROGATIVE_ENACTED_DESC">
			<Text>
				There are times, in spite of the will of government, that the sovereign must take action. In these times, the Royal Prerogative must be exercised for the good of the nation.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Current [ICON_JFD_REFORM_COOLDOWN] Reform Cooldown is halved.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Invoke Reserve Powers-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_RESERVE_POWERS">
			<Text>Invoke Reserve Powers</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_RESERVE_POWERS_DESC">
			<Text>
				There are times, in spite of the will of government, that the ruler must take immediate action. In these times, the Reserve Powers must be invoked for the good of the nation.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Requirements:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must be a Republic.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must have a Legislature.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]May only be enacted once per era.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Costs:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]4 [ICON_MAGISTRATES] Magistrates.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]A new [ICON_JFD_VOTE] Election is called.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_RESERVE_POWERS_ENACTED_DESC">
			<Text>
				There are times, in spite of the will of government, that the ruler must take immediate action. In these times, the Reserve Powers must be invoked for the good of the nation.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]A new [ICON_JFD_VOTE] Election is called.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Issue Holy Decree-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_HOLY_DECREE">
			<Text>Issue Holy Decree</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_HOLY_DECREE_DESC">
			<Text>There are times, in spite of the will of government, that the sovereign must take action. In these times, a Holy Decree must be issued for the good of the faith.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Requirements:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must be a Theocracy.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must have a Legislature.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]May only be enacted once per era.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Costs:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]4 {1_ResourceDesc}.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+{2_Num} [ICON_JFD_PIETY] Piety.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+50 [ICON_JFD_PIETY] Piety for all civilizations following your State Religion.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Note: the [ICON_JFD_PIETY] Piety reward that you receive increases for every Civilization following your State Religion.[ENDCOLOR]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_HOLY_DECREE_ENACTED_DESC">
			<Text>There are times, in spite of the will of government, that the sovereign must take action. In these times, a Holy Decree must be issued for the good of the faith.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Lump sum of [ICON_JFD_PIETY] Piety.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+50 [ICON_JFD_PIETY] Piety for all civilizations following your State Religion.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_HOLY_DECREE_CATHOLICISM">
			<Text>Issue Papal Bull</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Revoke the Holy Roman Empire-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_REVOKE_HOLY_ROME">
			<Text>Revoke the Holy Roman Empire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_REVOKE_HOLY_ROME_DESC">
			<Text>
				There are times, in spite of the will of government, that a system is not fit to serve its purpose. In these times, the Emperor must give up his duties and surrender the Holy Roman Empire.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Requirements:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must be the Holy Roman Empire.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must have a Legislature.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]May only be enacted once per era.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Costs:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]4 {1_ResourceDesc}.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Allows you to switch Government for free.
				[ICON_BULLET]+{1_Num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Note: the [ICON_CULTURE] Culture reward that you receive is based upon the Culture Per Turn of every Befriended City-State.[ENDCOLOR]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_REVOKE_HOLY_ROME_ENACTED_DESC">
			<Text>
				There are times, in spite of the will of government, that a system is not fit to serve its purpose. In these times, the Emperor must give up his duties and surrender the Holy Roman Empire.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Allows you to switch Government for free.
				[ICON_BULLET]Lump sum of [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Purge Enemies of the State-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_PURGE_ENEMIES">
			<Text>Purge Enemies of the State</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_PURGE_ENEMIES_DESC">
			<Text>
				There are times, in spite of the will of government, that the sovereign must take action. In these times, the state's enemies must be purged for the good of the nation.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Requirements:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must be a Dictatorship.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Must have a Legislature.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]May only be enacted once per era.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Costs:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]4 {1_ResourceDesc}.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][ICON_RESISTANCE] Anarchy is set to 0.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][ICON_RESISTANCE] Resistance is set to 0.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_JFD_PURGE_ENEMIES_ENACTED_DESC">
			<Text>
				There are times, in spite of the will of government, that the sovereign must take action. In these times, the state's enemies must be purged for the good of the nation.
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rewards:[ENDCOLOR]
				[NEWLINE]-------------------------
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][ICON_RESISTANCE] Anarchy is set to 0.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][ICON_RESISTANCE] Resistance is set to 0.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--MISSIONS-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MISSION_JFD_JOIN_COUNCIL">
			<Text>Join Advisory Council</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MISSION_JFD_JOIN_COUNCIL_HELP">
			<Text>This order will consume the Great Person and fill the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_Desc}[ENDCOLOR] position upon the Advisory Council.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]If the seat is already filled, the existing Councillor will be replaced.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MISSION_JFD_JOIN_COUNCIL_DISABLED_HELP">
			<Text>Unit must be stationed in a city and at full Health. You must also have established a Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--TECHS-->
		<!--Code of Laws-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_ALLOWS_GOVERNMENTS">
			<Text>Allows you to establish a Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--WONDERS-->
		<!--Amer Fort-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_AMER_FORT">
			<Text>Amer Fort</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_AMER_FORT_HELP">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength for units fighting in friendly territory. Provides a free Castle in the city in which it is built.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_AMER_FORT_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE]"He who is prudent and lies in wait for an enemy who is not, will be victorious"[NEWLINE] - Sun Tzu[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_AMER_FORT_PEDIA">
			<Text>Sometimes known as the Amber Fort, Amer Fort is a fortress found in the town of Amer, less than seven miles from Jaipur. Built on a hill by Raja Man Singh I, Amer Fort is a popular attraction for its artistic style and blending of Hindu and Rajput architecture. The fort overlooks the Maota Lake on a forested hill. During medieval India Amer was known as Dhundar and ruled by the Kachwahas, the fort itself was built in 1592 over the remnants of the earlier structure by Raja Man Singh I, a commander of Akbar the Great's army and a member of the Emperor's inner circle. His decendant, Jai Singh I expanded Amer Fort further. Beyond then Amer Fort continued the further improve with every ruler who followed for the next 150 years, until the Kachwahas shifted the capital to Jaipur during the reign of Sawai Jai Singh II in 1727.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Many of the original buildings of the medieval period have either been destroyed of replaced, the sixteenth century edifice however and the palace complex within build by the Rajput Maharajas is very well preserved. Amer Fort is split into four sections, each with its own gate and courtyard. The main entrance is the "Suraj Pole" - the Sun Gate - leading to the first courtyard. Armies held victory parades at the gate with their bounty. The gate was built for the purpose of protection, a garrison was posted to secure the main entry into the palace, and the gate itself faces east to greet the sun - where it takes its namesake. The first courtyard leads to the palace grounds and is resplendant with temples as well as the Ganesh Gate entering into the palaces. The second courtyard houses the Public Audience Hall; the Raja held audiences to heed petitions from the public. The Ganesh Gate opened into the third courtyard where the private quarters of the royal family and the servants were kept. This courtyard holds two buildings seperated but a garden fashioned similiarly to the Mughal Gardens. The two buildings are the "Jai Mandir", commonly known as the Sheesh Mahal - or Mirror Palace - and the "Sukh Niwas" or Sukh Mahal - the Hall of Pleasure. The Mirror Palace is known for its beautiful glass panels and mirror patterned ceilings. The fourth courtyard is where the royal family women resided, displaying a number of living rooms along a common corridor.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Doge's Palace-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_DOGES_PALACE">
			<Text>Doge's Palace</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_DOGES_PALACE_HELP">
			<Text>Requires Republic. +10% [ICON_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY] Sovereignty when all Cities have a [ICON_SWAP] Trade Route. Boosts relations with other Republics.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_DOGES_PALACE_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE]"There is no sanctuary so holy that money cannot profane it, no fortress so strong that money cannot take it by storm"[NEWLINE] - Marcus Tullius Cicero[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_DOGES_PALACE_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Doge's Palace is a palace built in Venetian Gothic style, and one of the main landmarks of the city of Venice in northern Italy. The palace was the residence of the Doge of Venice, the supreme authority of the former Republic of Venice, opening as a museum in 1923. Today, it is one of the 11 museums run by the Fondazione Musei Civici di Venezia.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPECIFIC_DIPLO_JFD_SAME_REPUBLIC">
			<Text>They like that you have chosen a Republic.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Dur Sharrukin-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_DUR_SHARRIKUN">
			<Text>Sargon's Palace</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_DUR_SHARRIKUN_HELP">
			<Text>Allows you to immediately establish a Government. Allows [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to be moved from any city along trade routes inside your civilization.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_DUR_SHARRIKUN_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"Sargon had neither rival nor equal. His splendor, over the lands it diffused. He marched to Kazallu and turned Kazallu into a ruin heap, so that there was not even a perch for a bird left." [NEWLINE] -  Chronicle of Early Kings[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_DUR_SHARRIKUN_PEDIA">
			<Text>Dur-Sharrukin, present day Khorsabad, was the Assyrian capital in the time of Sargon II of Assyria. The great city was entirely built in the decade preceding 706 BCE. After the unexpected death of Sargon in battle, the capital was shifted 20 km south to Nineveh.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Sargon II ruled from 722 to 705 BCE. In 717, Sargon ordered the construction of a new palace-city at the confluence of the Tigris and the Greater Zab rivers. The demands for timber and other materials and craftsmen, who came from as far as coastal Phoenicia, are documented in contemporary Assyrian letters. The debts of construction workers were nullified in order to attract a sufficient labour force. The land in the environs of the town was taken under cultivation, and olive groves were planted to increase Assyria's deficient oil-production. The great city was entirely built in the decade preceding 706 BCE, when the court moved to Dur-Sharrukin, although it was not completely finished yet. Sargon was killed during a battle in 705. After his unexpected death his son and successor Sennacherib abandoned the project, and relocated the capital with its administration to the city of Nineveh, 20 km south. The city was never completed and it was finally abandoned a century later when the Assyrian empire fell.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_DUR_SHARRIKUN_DOMESTIC">
			<Text>JFD: Sargon's Palace</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_DUR_SHARRIKUN_DOMESTIC_HELP">
			<Text>Allows [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to be moved from this city along trade routes inside your civilization.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Himeji Castle-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_HIMEJI_HELP">
			<Text>Allows establishing the unique Shogunate Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Hofburg Palace-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HOFBURG_PALACE">
			<Text>Hofburg Palace</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_HOFBURG_PALACE_HELP">
			<Text>Allows establishing the unique Holy Roman Empire Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_HOFBURG_PALACE_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE]"On Earth, God has placed no more than two powers, and as there is in Heaven but one God, so is there here one Pope and one Emperor. Divine providence has specially appointed the Roman Empire to prevent the continuance of schism in the Church." - Frederick I[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_HOFBURG_PALACE_PEDIA">
			<Text>Hofburg Palace is the former imperial palace in the centre of Vienna, Austria. Part of the palace forms the official residence and workplace of the President of Austria. Built in the 13th century and expanded in the centuries since, the palace has housed some of the most powerful people in European and Austrian history, including monarchs of the Habsburg dynasty, rulers of the Austro-Hungarian Empire. It was the principal imperial winter residence, as Schönbrunn Palace was their summer residence.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Since 1279 the Hofburg area has been the documented seat of government for various empires and republics. The Hofburg has been expanded over the centuries to include various residences (with the Amalienburg), the Imperial Chapel (Hofkapelle or Burgkapelle), the Naturhistorisches Museum and Kunsthistorisches Museum, the Austrian National Library (Hofbibliothek), the Imperial Treasury (Schatzkammer), the Burgtheater, the Spanish Riding School (Hofreitschule), the Imperial Horse Stables (Stallburg and Hofstallungen), and the Hofburg Congress Center.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--St. Peter's Basilica-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_ST_PETERS">
			<Text>St. Peter's Basilica</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_ST_PETERS_HELP">
			<Text>Requires Theocracy. +10% [ICON_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY] Sovereignty when at least [ICON_JFD_PIETY] Virtuous. Boosts relations with Monarchies and Republics that share your State Religion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_ST_PETERS_QUOTE">
			<Text>
				[NEWLINE]"A rock pile ceases to be a rock pile the moment a single man contemplates it, bearing within him the image of a cathedral"[NEWLINE] - Antoine de Saint-Exupery[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_ST_PETERS_PEDIA">
			<Text>Basilica Papale di San Pietro in Vaticano, better known as St. Peter's Basilica, is a late Renaissance church in Vatican City, with the largest interior of any Christian church in the world. The supposed burial site of the apostle Peter in 64 AD, some years later a shrine was constructed there. Replacing the shrine, construction of "old" St. Peter's was begun by the Emperor Constantine between 319 and 333 AD. Having fallen into serious disrepair over the centuries, Pope Julius II in 1505 determined to demolish the old church and replace it with a monumental structure, a construction project that spanned the next 120 years under a succession of popes and architects. To finance the colossal project, a number of popes authorized the wholesale selling of indulgences, a practice that led in part to Martin Luther's protestant movement. With work by some of the Renaissance's leading figures - Michelangelo, Raphael, Bramante, Bernini and others - the church now stands as one of the great treasures of Western civilization.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPECIFIC_DIPLO_JFD_SAME_THEOCRACY">
			<Text>They like that you are the head of their State Religions.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Versailles-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_VERSAILLES">
			<Text>Versailles</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_VERSAILLES_HELP">
			<Text>Requires Monarchy. +10% [ICON_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY] Sovereignty when all Cities have a [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work. Boosts relations with other Monarchies.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_VERSAILLES_THEME_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure all Great Works are Art</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_JFD_VERSAILLES">
			<Text>Château de Versailles</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_VERSAILLES_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE]"Every time I create an appointment, I create a hundred malcontents and one ingrate."[NEWLINE] - Louis XIV[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_VERSAILLES_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Château de Versailles is one of the most beautiful achievements of 18th-century French art. The site began as Louis XIII's hunting lodge before his son Louis XIV transformed and expanded it, moving the court and government of France to Versailles in 1682. Each of the three French kings who lived there until the French Revolution added improvements to make it more beautiful.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The château lost its standing as the official seat of power in 1789 but acquired a new role in the 19th century as the Museum of the History of France, which was founded at the behest of Louis-Philippe, who ascended to the throne in 1830. That is when many of the château's rooms were taken over to house the new collections, which were added to until the early 20th century, tracing milestones in French history.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPECIFIC_DIPLO_JFD_SAME_MONARCHY">
			<Text>They like that you have chosen a Monarchy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--YIELDS-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_YIELD_JFD_SOVEREIGNTY">
			<Text>Sovereignty</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>