<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 2/14/2017 6:15:06 AM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!--CONCEPTS-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_HEALTH_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Health: Introduction</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_HEALTH_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Health[ENDCOLOR] is the measurement of a city's habitability and is used to offset Disease. When a city has more Health than Disease, that Health contributes directly toward Food.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Disease[ENDCOLOR] is the opposite to Health. When a city has more Disease than Health, it may enter a period of Plague after too long. Disease is increased by Population, certain Features, Trade Routes, and certain Buildings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_HEALTH_INCREASE_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Health: Increasing Health</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_HEALTH_INCREASE_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>A city's [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Health[ENDCOLOR] is increased through the construction of buildings such as the Apothecary. It is also increased by a variety of Beliefs, Policies, Wonders, and other Buildings. There are also a numer of ways to reduce Disease.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_HEALTH_PLAGUE_HEADING1_TITLE">
			<Text>Health: Plague</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_HEALTH_PLAGUE_HEADING1_BODY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Plague[ENDCOLOR] is a temporary state in which Citizens consume additional Food and in which the city takes extra damage based upon City Disease. A period of Plague will occur if a city is more Diseased than it is Healthy for too long.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--BELIEFS-->
		<!--God of Medicine-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_JFD_GOD_MEDICINE_SHORT_DESC">
			<Text>God of Medicine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_JFD_GOD_MEDICINE_DESC">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from Herbalists</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--One with Nature-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_JFD_ONE_WITH_NATURE_DESC">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and +3 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from Natural Wonders</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Healing Vapors-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_JFD_HEALING_VAPORS_SHORT_DESC">
			<Text>Healing Vapors</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_JFD_HEALING_VAPORS_DESC">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from Marsh and Flood Plains</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Shamanism-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_JFD_SHAMANISM_SHORT_DESC">
			<Text>Shamanism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_JFD_SHAMANISM_DESC">
			<Text>Doctor specialists yield +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health and +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--BUILDINGS-->
		<!--Apothecary-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_APOTHECARY">
			<Text>Apothecary</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_APOTHECARY_HELP">
			<Text>City must have a Herbalist.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_APOTHECARY_HELP_CBO">
			<Text>City must have a Healer.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_APOTHECARY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Apothecary boosts the city's [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health. The city must possess a Herbalist before it can construct an Apothecary.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_APOTHECARY_TEXT">
			<Text>An apothecary is the name of a person who researches and creates herbal medicines (it's also the name of his business establishment). In ancient Persia, the practice of medicine was split between two professions. The "ashpiu" was a sort of sorcerer or witch-doctor, who determined the spiritual cause of the ailment and prescribed the religious and magical rituals necessary for a cure. The ashpiu could also refer the patient to an apothecary or "asu," a combination of pharmacist and physician, who would provide the necessary medicines and treatments to cure the ailment.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Aqueduct-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_AQUEDUCT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Aqueduct decreases the amount of Food a city needs to increase in size. It also increases the Health output of Lake and River Tiles. Build Aqueducts in cities that you want to grow large over time.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_AQUEDUCT_HELP_HEALTH">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health on Lake and River Tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_AQUEDUCT_HELP_HEALTH_REQ">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built next to a River.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Cistern-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_CISTERN">
			<Text>Cistern</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_CISTERN_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health on Lake Tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]40% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must NOT be built next to a River.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_CISTERN_HELP_CBO">
			<Text>City must NOT be built next to a River.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_CISTERN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Cistern decreases the amount of [ICON_FOOD] Food a city needs to increase in size. It also increases the [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health output of Lake Tiles. Build Cisterns in cities that you want to grow large over time, if they aren't on a river.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_CISTERN_STRATEGY_CBO">
			<Text>The Cistern increases a City's Health. Cisterns may only be constructed in cities that are not built on a river.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_CISTERN_TEXT">
			<Text>A cistern is a waterproof receptacle for holding liquids, usually water. Cisterns are often built to catch and store rainwater. Cisterns are distinguished from wells by their waterproof linings. Modern cisterns range in capacity from a few litres to thousands of cubic metres, effectively forming covered reservoirs.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Factory-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_FACTORY_HELP_HEALTH">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_JFD_DISEASE] Disease from [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Grocer-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_GROCER">
			<Text>Grocer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_GROCER_HELP">
			<Text>Each source of  [ICON_RES_COCOA] Cocoa, [ICON_RES_SPICES] Spices, and [ICON_RES_SUGAR] Sugar worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have at least one of these resources improved nearby.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_GROCER_HELP_EXCE">
			<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_COCOA] Cocoa, [ICON_RES_SPICES] Spices, [ICON_RES_SUGAR] Sugar, and [ICON_RES_JFD_VANILLA] Vanilla worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have at least one of these resources improved nearby.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_GROCER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Grocer is a early-game building designed to boost the [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health output of various Luxury Resources. A city must have a source of one of these resources before it can build a Grocer.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_GROCER_TEXT">
			<Text>Beginning as early as the 14th century, a grocer (or "purveyor") was a dealer in comestible dry goods such as spices, peppers, sugar, and (later) cocoa, tea and coffee. These items were bought in bulk, hence the term grocer from the French "grossier" meaning wholesaler, this term derived from Medieval Latin "grossarius" from which we also derive the word gross (meaning a quantity of twelve dozen, or 144). As increasing numbers of staple foodstuffs became available in cans and other less-perishable packaging, the trade expanded its province. Today, grocers deal in a wide range of staple food-stuffs including such perishables as meats, produce and dairy products. Such goods are, hence, groceries.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Harbour-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HARBOUR_HELP">
			<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_CRAB] Crab, [ICON_RES_FISH] Fish, [ICON_RES_PEARLS] Pearls, and [ICON_RES_WHALE] Whale worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Harbour (More Luxuries)-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HARBOUR_HELP_ML">
			<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_CORAL] Coral, [ICON_RES_CRAB] Crab, [ICON_RES_FISH] Fish, [ICON_RES_PEARLS] Pearls, and [ICON_RES_WHALE] Whale worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Herbalist-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HERBALIST">
			<Text>Herbalist</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HERBALIST_CBO">
			<Text>Healer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HERBALIST_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health on Flood Plain and Jungle Tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HERBALIST_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Herbalist boosts the city's [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health. It also increases [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from any Flood Plains or Jungles near to the City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HERBALIST_STRATEGY_CBO">
			<Text>The Healer boosts the city's [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health. It also increases [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from any Jungle Tiles near to the City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HERBALIST_TEXT">
			<Text>Herbalism is use of plants for medicinal purposes, and the study of such use. Plants have been the basis for medical treatments through much of human history, and such traditional medicine is still widely practiced today. Modern medicine recognizes herbalism as a form of alternative medicine, as the practice of herbalism is not strictly based on evidence gathered using the scientific method. Modern medicine, does, however, make use of many plant-derived compounds as the basis for evidence-tested pharmaceutical drugs, and phytotherapy works to apply modern standards of effectiveness testing to herbs and medicines that are derived from natural sources.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HERBALIST_TEXT_CBO">
			<Text>Traditional medicine (also known as indigenous or folk medicine) comprises knowledge systems that developed over generations within various societies before the era of modern medicine. The World Health Organization (WHO) defines traditional medicine as "the sum total of the knowledge, skills, and practices based on the theories, beliefs, and experiences indigenous to different cultures, whether explicable or not, used in the maintenance of health as well as in the prevention, diagnosis, improvement or treatment of physical and mental illness."</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Hospital-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HOSPITAL_HELP">
			<Text>-33% [ICON_JFD_DISEASE] Disease from [ICON_CITIZEN] Population in this city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an Apothecary.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HOSPITAL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Hospital is an Industrial-era building. It boosts the city's [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health and reduces [ICON_JFD_DISEASE] Disease from [ICON_CITIZEN] Population. The city must possess an Apothecary before it can construct a Hospital.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Grain Elevator-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_GRAIN_SILO">
			<Text>Grain Elevator</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_GRAIN_SILO_HELP">
			<Text>City must have a Granary.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_GRAIN_SILO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Grain Elevator is a Modern-era building. It's useful when you want to create a large city, fast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_GRAIN_SILO_TEXT">
			<Text>In the grain trade, a grain elevator is a tower containing a bucket elevator or a pneumatic conveyor, which scoops up grain from a lower level and deposits it in a silo or other storage facility. In most cases, the term "grain elevator" also covers the entire elevator complex (an example of pars pro toto), including receiving and testing offices, weighbridges, storage facilities etc. It may also mean organizations that operate or control several individual elevators, in different locations. In Australia the term grain elevator refers to the lifting mechanism only.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Longhouse-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_LONGHOUSE_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from each worked Forest tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_LONGHOUSE_HELP_CBO">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from each worked Forest tile. Requires a nearby, workable Forest or Jungle tile to be constructed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_LONGHOUSE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Longhouse is the Iroquois unique building, replacing the Workshop. It increases the city's [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health output for each forest within the city's radius. </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_LONGHOUSE_STRATEGY_CBO">
			<Text>The Longhouse is the Iroquois unique building, replacing the Healer. It increases the city's [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health output for each forest within the city's radius.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Monastery-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_MONASTERY_HELP_HEALTH">
			<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_INCENSE] Incense and [ICON_RES_WINE] Wine worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_MONASTERY_STRATEGY_HEALTH">
			<Text>Monasteries increase a city's [ICON_PEACE] Faith, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health output, especially if the city is near to improved Incense and/or Wine resources.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_MONASTERY_HELP_HEALTH_EXCE">
			<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_INCENSE] Incense, [ICON_RES_JFD_SAFFRON] Saffron, and [ICON_RES_WINE] Wine worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_MONASTERY_STRATEGY_HEALTH_EXCE">
			<Text>Monasteries increase a city's [ICON_PEACE] Faith, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health output, especially if the city is near to improved Incense, Saffron, and/or Wine resources.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Recylcing Center-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_RECYCLING_CENTER_HELP">
			<Text>Eliminates [ICON_JFD_DISEASE] Disease from Buildings. Maximum of 5 of these buildings in your empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_RECYCLING_CENTER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Each Recycling Center provides 2 [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum. Maximum of 5 of these buildings in your empire. Also eliminates all [ICON_JFD_DISEASE] Disease produced by Buildings in the city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Supermarket-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_SUPERMARKET">
			<Text>Supermarket</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_SUPERMARKET_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health on [ICON_RES_BANANA] Banana, [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison, [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle, [ICON_RES_DEER] Deer, [ICON_RES_FISH] Fish, and [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have at least one of these resources improved nearby.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_SUPERMARKET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Supermarket is a late-game building designed to boost the [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health output of various Bonus Resources. A city must have a source of one of these resources before it can build a Supermarket.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_SUPERMARKET_TEXT">
			<Text>Supermarkets are large, self-service retail stores that sell a wide variety of food items and household goods to the general public. The first true supermarket, King Kullen, was established in 1930 in the borough of Queens, New York City, by Michael Cullen. Improved storage techniques and refrigeration allowed supermarkets to stock and sell perishable foods in large quantities, reducing the price to the consumer. The combination of ready availability and low prices made the supermarket an instant success in the U.S. during the years of the Great Depression. The supermarket continues to grow in popularity in countries around the world. </Text>
		</Row>
		<!--NATIONAL WONDERS-->
		<!--Red Cross-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_RED_CROSS">
			<Text>Red Cross</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_RED_CROSS_HELP">
			<Text>Decreases [ICON_JFD_PLAGUE] Plague chance by 25%.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All newly trained Units in this City begin with the Medic promotion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a Hospital in all Cities. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_RED_CROSS_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Red Cross decreases the chance of [ICON_JFD_PLAGUE] Plague breaking out in your empire. A civilization must have a Hospital in all cities before it can construct the Red Cross.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_RED_CROSS_TEXT">
			<Text>While fundamentally in conflict with the destructive goals of war, physicians must still proffer aid to those in need. The practice of repairing the personal damage of war, sometimes actually during the fight itself, has a number of benefits beyond the obvious. A paramount one is that of morale, since the soldiers of an army that contains surgeons are assured care if they fall in battle.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--IMPROVEMENTS-->
		<!--Plague-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_JFD_PLAGUE">
			<Text>Plague</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Sanatorium-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_JFD_SANATORIUM">
			<Text>Construct a Sanatorium</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_JFD_SANATORIUM_HELP">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Great Tile Improvements will connect Strategic Resources on this tile to the trade network.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_JFD_SANATORIUM">
			<Text>Sanatorium</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_JFD_SANATORIUM_TEXT">
			<Text>A sanatorium is a medical facility for long-term illness, most typically associated with treatment of tuberculosis (TB) before antibiotics. A distinction is sometimes made between "sanitarium" (a kind of health resort, as in the Battle Creek Sanitarium) and "sanatorium" (a hospital).</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--MISSIONS-->
		<!--Cure Plague-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MISSION_JFD_CURE_PLAGUE">
			<Text>Cure Plague</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MISSION_JFD_CURE_PLAGUE_HELP">
			<Text>This order will consume the unit and removes the city's [ICON_JFD_PLAGUE] Plague, as well as any progress toward [ICON_JFD_PLAGUE] Plague.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MISSION_JFD_CURE_PLAGUE_DISABLED">
			<Text>Unit must be stationed in a city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Distribute Vaccinations-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MISSION_JFD_POPULATION">
			<Text>Distribute Vaccinations</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MISSION_JFD_POPULATION_HELP">
			<Text>This order will consume the unit and grant +1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen in all cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MISSION_JFD_POPULATION_DISABLED">
			<Text>Unit must be stationed in a city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--PLAGUES-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_AIDS">
			<Text>AIDS</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_ALCOHOL">
			<Text>Alcohol Poisoning</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_BONES">
			<Text>Brittle Bone Disease</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_BRONCHITIS">
			<Text>Bronchitis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_BUBONIC">
			<Text>Black Death</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_CANCER">
			<Text>Cancer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_CHOLERA">
			<Text>Cholera</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_DANCING">
			<Text>Dancing Mania</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_DENGUE">
			<Text>Dengue Fever</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_DYSENTERY">
			<Text>Dysentery</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_FATIGUE">
			<Text>Fatigue</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_FEVER">
			<Text>Relapsing Fever</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_FOOD">
			<Text>Food Poisoning</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_HIVES">
			<Text>Hives</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_IMPOTENCE">
			<Text>Impotence</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_INFLUENZA">
			<Text>Influenza</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_GOUT">
			<Text>Gout</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_LEG">
			<Text>Restless Leg Syndrome</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_LEPROSY">
			<Text>Leprosy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_LOCKJAW">
			<Text>Lockjaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_LUNACY">
			<Text>Lunacy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_MALAISE">
			<Text>Malaise</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_MEASLES">
			<Text>Measles</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_MENIERE">
			<Text>Meniere's Disease</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_POSSESSION">
			<Text>Possession</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_PNEUMONIA">
			<Text>Pneumonia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_RABIES">
			<Text>Rabies</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_SCURVY">
			<Text>Scurvy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_SEPTICEMIA">
			<Text>Septicemic Plague</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_SIDS">
			<Text>SIDS</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_SLEEPING">
			<Text>Sleeping Sickness</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_SMALLPOX">
			<Text>Smallpox</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_SYPHILIS">
			<Text>Syphilis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_SUICIDE">
			<Text>Suicideation</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_TUBERCULOSIS">
			<Text>Consumption</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_TYPHOID">
			<Text>Slow Fever</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_TYPHUS">
			<Text>Camp Fever</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_WEILS">
			<Text>Weil's Disease</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_YELLOW">
			<Text>Yellow Fever</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAGUE_JFD_ZIKA">
			<Text>Zika Virus</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--POLICIES-->
		<!--Piety Opener-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_JFD_PIETY_HELP_HEALTH">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Piety[ENDCOLOR] increases the [ICON_PEACE] Faith of empires.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Adopting Piety allows you to build Shrines and Temples in half the usual time. Unlocks building the Great Mosque of Djenne.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Adopting all Policies in the Piety tree causes a Great Prophet to appear and Holy Sites provide +3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. It also allows the purchase of Great Doctors with [ICON_PEACE] Faith starting in the Industrial Era.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Organised Religion-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_JFD_ORGANIZED_RELIGION_HELP_HEALTH">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Organized Religion[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from Shrines and Temples.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_JFD_ORGANIZED_RELIGION_HELP_HEALTH_CBO">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Organized Religion[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]-25% [ICON_PEACE] Faith purchase costs. +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from Shrines and Temples.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Tradition Opener-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_JFD_TRADITION_HELP_HEALTH">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Tradition[ENDCOLOR] is best for small empires.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Adopting Tradition greatly increases the rate of border expansion in cities and also grants 3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital. Unlocks building the Hanging Gardens.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Adopting all Policies in the Tradition tree will grant +15% [ICON_FOOD] Growth and a free Aqueduct or Cistern in your first 4 cities (up to 2 of each). It also allows the purchase of Great Engineers with peace Faith starting in the Industrial Era.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--SPECIALISTS-->
		<!--Doctor-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPECIALIST_JFD_DOCTOR">
			<Text>Doctor|Doctors</Text>
			<Plurality>1|2</Plurality>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPECIALIST_JFD_DOCTOR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Create Doctors to increase the empire's [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health and to speed the creation of Great Doctors.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPECIALIST_JFD_DOCTOR_SLOTS">
			<Text>Doctor Slots:</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPECIALIST_JFD_DOCTOR_TITLE">
			<Text>Great Doctor Points:</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--TECHS-->
		<!--Medicine-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TECH_JFD_MEDICINE_TITLE">
			<Text>Medicine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TECH_JFD_MEDICINE_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"As to diseases, make a habit of two things - to help or at least to do no harm."[NEWLINE] - Hippocrates [NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TECH_JFD_MEDICINE_DESC">
			<Text>Primitive man attributed the onset of serious disease as the influence of the gods, or possession by evil spirits. Over time, however, it was found that such "possessions" could be treated through the use of elixirs made from plant extracts. Methods were also developed to clean and treat wounds, and set fractured bones. The ancient Greeks established the first schools to teach medical sciences circa 500 BC. The texts produced by the students of these schools, most notably Hippocrates, who is considered the father of medicine, based his theories of the human body on observation and reasoning rather than supernatural intervention.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Continued study of diseases over the years, combined with the dissection and study of the human body in the 13th century, pointed out flaws in early Greek theories, and led to more accurate medical texts based on detailed analysis rather than conjecture. By the 18th century, the same methods of analysis and observation used by scientists in other fields were applied to the study of medicine. This paved the way for the increasingly effective methods of treatment and surgery that have prevailed over the last 200 years.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TECH_JFD_MEDICINE_HELP">
			<Text>Allows you to construct the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Apothecary[ENDCOLOR], which increases a city's [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Theology-->
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_TECH_JFD_THEOLOGY_HELP">
			<Text>Allows you to build a handful of specialized Wonders which improve your [ICON_PEACE] Faith output.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<!--TENETS-->
		<!--Decriminlization-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_JFD_DECRIMINALIZATION_HELP_HEALTH">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Decriminalization[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]Reduces [ICON_JFD_CRIME_BLACK] Crime from [ICON_JFD_CRIME_HEALTH] Possession, [ICON_JFD_CRIME_HAPPINESS] Treason, and [ICON_JFD_CRIME_CULTURE] Vandalism by 20% in all Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Universal Healthcare-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_JFD_UNIVERSAL_HEALTHCARE_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Universal Healthcare[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]-22% [ICON_JFD_DISEASE] Disease from [ICON_CITIZEN] Population.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--WONDERS-->
		<!--Angkor Wat-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_ANGKOR_WAT_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from Holy Sites.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Hanging Gardens-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_HANGING_GARDENS_HELP">
			<Text>Provides a free Garden in the city in which it is built. +1 [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health from every Garden.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Pont du Gard-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JFD_PONT_DU_GARD">
			<Text>Pont du Gard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_PONT_DU_GARD_HELP">
			<Text>+20% [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Excess Health is converted to [ICON_FOOD] Food. Provides a free Aqueduct in the city in which it is built.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built next to a River.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_PONT_DU_GARD_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE]"Will anybody compare the Pyramids, or those useless though renowned works of the Greeks, with these aqueducts?"[NEWLINE] - Frontinus[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_JFD_PONT_DU_GARD_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Pont du Gard is an ancient Roman aqueduct that crosses the Gardon River in the south of France. Located near the town of Vers-Pont-du-Gard, the bridge is part of the Nîmes aqueduct, a 50-kilometer system built in the first century AD to carry water from a spring at Uzès to the Roman colony of Nemausus (Nîmes). Because of the uneven terrain between the two points, the mostly underground aqueduct followed a long, winding route that called for a bridge across the gorge of the Gardon River. The Pont du Gard is the highest of all elevated Roman aqueducts, and, along with the Aqueduct of Segovia, one of the best preserved. It was added to UNESCO's list of World Heritage Sites in 1985 because of its historical importance.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--UNITS-->
		<!--Great Doctor-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR">
			<Text>Great Doctor</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_TEXT">
			<Text>"Great Doctors" are at the forefront of medicine, helping to extend and support human life. They seek out new cures for diseases, guide people to lead fulfilling lives, and help us to understand the human condition.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>A Great Doctor can construct the special Sanatorium improvement, which, when worked, provides a lot of [ICON_JFD_HEALTH] Health for a city. The Great Doctor may also be expended to increase the Population of all cities by +1. A Great Doctor may also be used to cure Plague from all Cities and to reset their Plague Progress to 0. A Great Doctor begins with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Medic[ENDCOLOR] promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_1">
			<Text>Thomas Becket</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_2">
			<Text>Hippocrates</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_3">
			<Text>Sir Magdi Yacoub</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_4">
			<Text>Samuel Hahnemann</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_5">
			<Text>Claudius Galenus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_6">
			<Text>Madhavakara</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_7">
			<Text>Chakrapani Datta</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_8">
			<Text>Zakaria al-Razi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_9">
			<Text>Ibn Sina</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_10">
			<Text>Ibn Rushd</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_11">
			<Text>Pierre Fauchard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_12">
			<Text>Moshe ben Maimon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_13">
			<Text>Galen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_14">
			<Text>Theophrast von Hohenheim</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_15">
			<Text>Garcia de Orta</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_16">
			<Text>Ambroise Pare</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_17">
			<Text>Charaka</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_18">
			<Text>Andreas Vesalius</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_19">
			<Text>William Harvey</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_20">
			<Text>Ole Wormius</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_21">
			<Text>Marcello Malpighi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_22">
			<Text>Richard Lower</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_23">
			<Text>Thomas Sydenham</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_24">
			<Text>Jean Astruc</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_25">
			<Text>Gregory House</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_26">
			<Text>Edward Jenner</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_27">
			<Text>Rene Theophile Hyacinthe Laennec</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_28">
			<Text>William McBride</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_29">
			<Text>John Snow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_30">
			<Text>Theodor Kocher</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_31">
			<Text>Ignaz Semmelweis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_32">
			<Text>William Worrall Mayo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_33">
			<Text>Joseph Lister</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_34">
			<Text>Theodor Billroth</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_35">
			<Text>Jean-Martin Charcot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_36">
			<Text>Ernst Haeckel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_37">
			<Text>Robert Koch</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_38">
			<Text>William Osler</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_39">
			<Text>Sigmund Freud</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_40">
			<Text>Christiaan Eijkman</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_41">
			<Text>Carl Gustav Jung</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_42">
			<Text>William James Mayo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_43">
			<Text>Charles Horace Mayo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_44">
			<Text>Charles Jean Henri Nicolle</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_45">
			<Text>Carlos Chaga</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_46">
			<Text>Allen Oldfather Whipple</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_47">
			<Text>Otto Fritz Meyerhof</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_48">
			<Text>George Richards Minot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_49">
			<Text>Oswaldo Cruz</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_50">
			<Text>Wilder Penfield</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_51">
			<Text>Frederick Banting</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_52">
			<Text>Charles R. Drew</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_53">
			<Text>Virginia Apgar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_54">
			<Text>Jonas Salk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_55">
			<Text>Joseph Ransohoff</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_56">
			<Text>Christiaan Barnard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_57">
			<Text>Daniel Carleton Gajdusek</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_58">
			<Text>Susruta</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_59">
			<Text>Carlo Urbani</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_60">
			<Text>Dioscorides</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_61">
			<Text>Abu al-Qasim al-Zahrawi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_62">
			<Text>Merit-Ptah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_63">
			<Text>Raba-sa-Marduk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_64">
			<Text>Peseshet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_65">
			<Text>Hesy-Ra</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_66">
			<Text>Agnodice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_67">
			<Text>Qar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_68">
			<Text>Simeon Seth</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_69">
			<Text>Tehorenhaegnon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_70">
			<Text>Esagil-kin-apli</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_72">
			<Text>Zhang Zhongjing</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_73">
			<Text>Huangfu Mi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_74">
			<Text>Vladimir Filatov</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_75">
			<Text>Nikolai Amosov</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_76">
			<Text>Danylo Zabolotny</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_77">
			<Text>Ivan Puluj</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_78">
			<Text>Florence Nightingale</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_79">
			<Text>Betsi Cadwaladr</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_80">
			<Text>Dorothy Price</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_81">
			<Text>Vagbhata</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_82">
			<Text>Jules Bordet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_83">
			<Text>Arvo Ylppö</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_84">
			<Text>Robert Tigerstedt</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_GREAT_DOCTOR_85">
			<Text>Ragnar Granit</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--YIELDS-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_YIELD_JFD_DISEASE">
			<Text>Disease</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_YIELD_JFD_HEALTH">
			<Text>Health</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>